<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>celebrate on Freshly Married</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/tags/celebrate/</link><description>Recent content in celebrate on Freshly Married</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://freshlymarried.github.io/tags/celebrate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Twin Baby Registry</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/twin-baby-registry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/twin-baby-registry/</guid><description>This post contains affiliate links to Amazon. Which means Freshly Married can make a small commission on items you buy through these links.
Well we are pretty much all prepared for our boys to come! At least, with the material items and their room &amp;hellip; mentally, I’m not sure yet! Haha. It feels weird that at 31 weeks we already bought everything on our registry that was left over from the generous gifts we received at our baby showers!</description></item><item><title>Gender Reveal!</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/gender-reveal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/gender-reveal/</guid><description>Everything about this pregnancy has been super exciting, not just for us but for our family and friends. I mean, it took us so much to finally get here, but we also get to experience the rare situation of twins! It&amp;rsquo;s also my in-laws&amp;rsquo; first grandbaby so it&amp;rsquo;s ALL very exciting for them.
So of course, we did a gender reveal party to share the sex of our identical twins with our family!</description></item><item><title>My Words of The Year</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/my-words-of-the-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/my-words-of-the-year/</guid><description>Now that the secret is out that I’m pregnant with twins I can finally share my words of the year because it has everything to do with them. :) I say WORDS because I think it&amp;rsquo;s important to have a goal in mind for you as an individual, and then a goal in mind for your marriage. However you like to do your goals, whether by choosing a specific word to inspire you, a vision board, or simply writing down the goal in a sentence, make sure you are considering how you can strengthen your marriage.</description></item><item><title>Christmas Card to Your Spouse!</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/christmas-card-to-your-spouse/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/christmas-card-to-your-spouse/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been so focused on what items to buy for my husband that I forgot about the gift of words that I could give him. Have you ever thought to give your spouse a Christmas card? We can write notes to our spouse on random occasions, or write them a letter for your wedding anniversary, or birthday. But I don&amp;rsquo;t think many of us use the opportunity of writing them a Christmas card or letter.</description></item><item><title>We Wash You A Happy Holiday!</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/we-wash-you-a-happy-holiday/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/we-wash-you-a-happy-holiday/</guid><description>This is for crafters AND non-crafters! *this blog post contains affiliate links through Amazon.
I&amp;rsquo;m a huge crafter and designed these gift tags for holiday gifts to some of our neighbors! I own a Cricut machine and have basically had it out all season long doing holiday stuff! I&amp;rsquo;ve recently ventured out exploring the other design tools it has in the program and using more than just the die-cutting option. YEP IT CAN WRITE.</description></item><item><title>25 White Elephant Gift Ideas</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/25-white-elephant-gift-ideas/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/25-white-elephant-gift-ideas/</guid><description>This post contains affiliate links to Amazon.
What’s a “White Elephant” gift? It’s a silly gag gift usually for playing a White Elephant game!
How does it work? There&amp;rsquo;s a pile of gifts, one per person who is playing. Everyone draws a number which decides the order they choose a gift from the pile. If you have 13 people/13 gifts, you’ll have numbers 1-13 to draw from. Starting with person #1, they will choose a gift from the pile to unwrap and reveal to everyone.</description></item><item><title>50 Gift Ideas for Your Spouse</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/50-gift-ideas-for-your-spouse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/50-gift-ideas-for-your-spouse/</guid><description>Every birthday, Christmas, Valentine’s Day, and wedding anniversary, I find myself googling thoughtful gift ideas that I can buy or make for my spouse. The same thing happens when I want to get a “just because” gift for him, or create a special date night for us. Add these up and we’ve got AT LEAST 5 times throughout the year searching for gift ideas.
Over the past few years, I have been keeping track of some awesome finds that interest me or my spouse, and I think most spouses would love too.</description></item><item><title>3 Tips For Preventing Holiday Stress From Affecting Your Marriage</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/3-tips-for-preventing-holiday-stress-from-affecting-your-marriage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/3-tips-for-preventing-holiday-stress-from-affecting-your-marriage/</guid><description>We are all well aware that while the holiday season can be a wonderful time of year spent with loved ones, it can also bring with it some stress. Just a few examples: spending hours trying to make your house look festive; thinking of the perfect gifts for family, friends, neighbors, and coworkers, then having to go get those gifts and wrap them, while trying to not spend a fortune; making special food for the celebrations; and feeling pressure to make special memories.</description></item><item><title>Back to School Interview For Your Spouse</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/back-to-school-interview-for-your-spouse/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/back-to-school-interview-for-your-spouse/</guid><description>Back to School InterviewThis is inspired by an email newsletter I received titled, &amp;ldquo;Interviews aren&amp;rsquo;t just for adults,&amp;rdquo; where I saw a cute picture of a kid holding up one of those back to school/all about me interview papers that people tend to do with their kids every year. And I instantly had a contradicting thought: &amp;ldquo;Back to school interviews aren&amp;rsquo;t just for kids!&amp;rdquo; haha. Which then inspired a great thought&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>A Joyful Marriage - Week 26</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-joyful-marriage-week-26/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-joyful-marriage-week-26/</guid><description>Today is my husband&amp;rsquo;s 26th birthday! Crazy enough, it happens to also be week 26 of this project, too! I love coincidences like that. And it works out well because the joy I have found in my marriage this week, is having that feeling like we know each other pretty well for our birthdays.
We&amp;rsquo;ve celebrated 5 birthdays together now, which is 10 birthdays total! Weird when you think about it in total numbers, right?</description></item><item><title>A Joyful Marriage - Week 19</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-joyful-marriage-week-19/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-joyful-marriage-week-19/</guid><description>The joy I found in my marriage this week: feeling a positive difference in our lives and our relationship. It&amp;rsquo;s a good feeling when both of you notice that your interactions and overall days feel different from the past few months. I think one of the biggest things that we both appreciated and found joy in was how we focused more on &amp;ldquo;listening to understand&amp;rdquo; when we discussed specific subjects. I&amp;rsquo;ve always known this principle but sometimes you just need to be reminded, right?</description></item><item><title>A Joyful Marriage - Week 11</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-joyful-marriage-week-11/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-joyful-marriage-week-11/</guid><description>The joy I found in my marriage this week: We missed each other while on our separate trips. And that says a lot to me. We both went on separate little trips this past week and we enjoyed them. Trevor&amp;rsquo;s was for business, and mine was for leisure, haha. We spent only 3 and a half days apart, which felt long for us considering the last time we spent more than one night apart was 3 years ago!</description></item><item><title>A Unique and Easy Homemade Card</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-unique-and-easy-homemade-card/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-unique-and-easy-homemade-card/</guid><description>*This post contains affiliate links.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know a marriage that doesn&amp;rsquo;t give cards or love notes to each other for special occasions or even just for no reason at all! They can seem boring sometimes unless you get a funny one, or one that just has that unique factor&amp;hellip;
WELL. I&amp;rsquo;m going to show you how to make the EASIEST unique card you&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen! It folds and opens in a fun way, you can make at home with supplies you most likely have laying around, and you can embellish it however you want!</description></item><item><title>Be Joyful</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/be-joyful/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/be-joyful/</guid><description>Since this is our 3rd attempt at Christmas cards, I kinda feel like I got it right. Maybe! I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like I could put together a newsletter super quickly even though I already had our template from last year. Something inside me suggested making it somewhat more simple this year. But I like to give more than just the picture of us with a small Christmas phrase with our names on it.</description></item><item><title>A Perfectly Imperfect Reminder</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-perfectly-imperfect-reminder/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-perfectly-imperfect-reminder/</guid><description>Today is a special day :) Four years ago on October 25th, Trevor and I made our relationship official. See, it was declared on facebook so it was official &amp;hellip; haha
This morning I went through my old journal from that time we were first dating and it was so special to go back and read all of that. I obviously knew our timeline and the words we said but there was something so tender about reading about it all, and especially my feelings during the rise of our relationship.</description></item><item><title>Wife Life is The Best Life</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/wife-life-is-the-best-life/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/wife-life-is-the-best-life/</guid><description>Super excited to announce that Freshly Married now has a t-shirt line on Etsy!
I love this phrase because though being a spouse has its difficult moments, it&amp;rsquo;s still such a rewarding life! This phrase is all about looking at the positive in marriage! There have been a few rough things we&amp;rsquo;ve had to experience in our marriage, but even in those times I find myself taking on this mindset, that the good outweighs the bad, and that I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t rather be with anyone else :)</description></item><item><title>The Real 'Love Your Spouse' Challenge</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-real-love-your-spouse-challenge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-real-love-your-spouse-challenge/</guid><description>[sc name=&amp;ldquo;soundcloud&amp;rdquo; id=&amp;ldquo;282060156&amp;rdquo; ]
So I got nominated to do that &amp;lsquo;Love Your Spouse&amp;rsquo; Challenge, but I&amp;rsquo;m not going to do it. It might be surprising since I&amp;rsquo;m a huge advocate of marriage, and that I totally admire this challenge going around! It&amp;rsquo;s important to publically share your feelings about your spouse, acknowledge their talents and how they have influenced your marriage, etc. But I think there can be TOO much of that sometimes.</description></item><item><title>6 Ways to Prioritize Your Spouse</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/6-ways-to-prioritize-your-spouse/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/6-ways-to-prioritize-your-spouse/</guid><description>A reader asked what I would suggest as ways to prioritize your spouse, and I decided to put all that information in a post because my reply is too big for a comment box! haha. So here&amp;rsquo;s my reply to my previous post: &amp;ldquo;Prioritizing My Spouse.&amp;rdquo;
The idea of growing apart happens gradually over time. When you think about it, there will always be sudden situations that come up where you do need to be there for your kids over your spouse, but I think the problem starts when this is happening frequently.</description></item><item><title>10 Ways to Journal Your Life Together</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/10-ways-to-journal-your-life-together/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/10-ways-to-journal-your-life-together/</guid><description>*this post contains affiliate links.
I recently looked through the scrapbook I made of our first year together, and it was fun taking this trip down memory lane, again! How special it is to look back through journals, or scrapbooks, and other mementos, and recover a taste of a memorable moment. One of those memories is this one that I made a scrapbook page out of :) It was the day we moved into our first apartment!</description></item><item><title>The Married Journal</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-married-journal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-married-journal/</guid><description>I love being right in the middle of a memorable moment when a certain kind of happiness overcomes me, and I can’t help but think, “I will never forget this.” Those moments are deemed “memorable” for whatever reason, and can stay in our hearts forever. As much as we wish they can be replayed over and over, they can’t be; unless you have a time machine in the form of a flying DeLorean, and your name is Doctor Emmett Brown.</description></item><item><title>First Big Vacation</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/first-big-vacation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/first-big-vacation/</guid><description>So I&amp;rsquo;m finally sharing our beautiful trip to Hawaii we took in May! Two phrases I remember saying multiple times out loud and in mind are: &amp;ldquo;Bucket list item - CHECK!&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s another new thing I can say I tried!&amp;rdquo; I liked being able to make those little steps of progression in life, but doing them felt a million times more special and held more purpose getting to do them with my husband :)</description></item><item><title>Message In a Bottle</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/message-in-a-bottle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/message-in-a-bottle/</guid><description>Every anniversary we do a little something to celebrate our love! Like everyone else! haha. Some people choose to follow the theme of their year from that list of anniversary gifts here. I guess I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be told what to get my spouse because my spouse is unique! Our gift to each other was celebrating in Hawaii this year, but I wanted us to do something special there to mark the occasion.</description></item><item><title>The Three-Year Milestone</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-three-year-milestone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-three-year-milestone/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve been following along from the beginning, you&amp;rsquo;ll remember that I wrote about the following married milestones: being married for three weeks, and then three months. So naturally, I felt like doing a milestone post on being married for THREE YEARS! That&amp;rsquo;s such a small number, but I believe every year is an accomplishment! And we&amp;rsquo;ve experienced so much together in this short time, so it gets me excited about what we&amp;rsquo;ll experience at our 30-year mark!</description></item><item><title>The Best Reason to go on a Vacation</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-best-reason-to-go-on-a-vacation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-best-reason-to-go-on-a-vacation/</guid><description>For the last year, we have been looking into a big vacation for ourselves. We&amp;rsquo;ve done research to various places, planning, and multiple times were minutes away from actually booking a trip! Yet we haven&amp;rsquo;t pulled the trigger&amp;hellip; until now! We finally did it - we went to HAWAII! Some of you might be saying, &amp;ldquo;Going to Hawaii is this big for you guys?&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;We go on vacations all the time&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Well, it&amp;rsquo;s different for us, and because it&amp;rsquo;s not something we do often, it will be that much more special :)</description></item><item><title>Being a Married College Student</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/being-a-married-college-student/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/being-a-married-college-student/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m grateful that I was able to experience college being both single, and then married. In the beginning I was doing the college thing for the experience and learning, but finishing college as a married woman for the last few semesters was for more than that. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t just doing it for me anymore.
The Single College Life People tend to think that it&amp;rsquo;s best to go through college being single, or at least not yet married.</description></item><item><title>Stop Rolling Your Eyes</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/stop-rolling-your-eyes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/stop-rolling-your-eyes/</guid><description>To the older couple staring at us kissing in line, stop rolling your eyes about it.
To the people sick of listening to proposal stories, stop rolling your eyes about it.
To the people who joke about my husband and I being prom dates because we sometimes match his tie and my dress for church, stop rolling your eyes about it.
Why am I saying this? Because people tend to get annoyed of young love and it bugs me.</description></item><item><title>The Importance of Family Photos</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-importance-of-family-photos/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-importance-of-family-photos/</guid><description>As you have noticed, we got some new family photos done :) And I&amp;rsquo;m loving them! I had been watching my friend Nicky post so many amazing pictures she has taken of families and couples, and knew that she could give us the memorable photos we were looking for. Throughout the process I was so impressed with her professionalism, expertise, artistic eye, and even encouragement that we looked cute, haha. I just had a really great experience with her and wanted to mention that as I share a few photos from this shoot.</description></item><item><title>Scrambled Eggs For the Win</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/scrambled-eggs-for-the-win/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/scrambled-eggs-for-the-win/</guid><description>I know pictures of food are annoying but there&amp;rsquo;s a reason I&amp;rsquo;m documenting it! We have obviously had to overhaul our meals with my food allergies, and it has been a whole bunch of trial and error. I&amp;rsquo;ve started to notice the affects in my body when I have even a little bit of something dairy here or there. I thought I could get away with cheating even just 2 tablespoons of ranch once a week but NOPE, haha.</description></item><item><title>Financial Independence</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/financial-independence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/financial-independence/</guid><description>In our short three years (almost) being married, Trevor and I have done really well about trying to be financially independent from our families. It&amp;rsquo;s something that had to be done in stages because tackling health insurance, car insurance, and a phone bill all at once is not wise! Health insurance is a headache on its own, am I right?! But slowly we made goals of what responsibilities we needed to take on and when to do it.</description></item><item><title>#freshdatenights Giveaway: $75 Amazon Gift Card!</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/#freshdatenights-giveaway-75-amazon-gift-card/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/#freshdatenights-giveaway-75-amazon-gift-card/</guid><description>I had a good luck charm apparently for this St. Patricks Day because I &amp;ldquo;won&amp;rdquo; some amazing seats to the Jazz game that night! I say &amp;ldquo;won&amp;rdquo; because an old friend couldn&amp;rsquo;t use them so they did a little drawing for people interested and I got them :) What&amp;rsquo;s better than a fun date night to an NBA game? A FREE ONE, haha. It was double-y awesome because Trevor and I had never been to a game together yet.</description></item><item><title>25</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/25/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/25/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve hit the quarter-life mark turning 25 last week and I feel the need to write about it. I have to say that I was not looking forward to this birthday just because the things I was wanting to do /to eat (but for reals!) I couldn&amp;rsquo;t have, or were out of reach. I thought that those things would make me happy. I have to admit that I totally cheated on my birthday and had two slices of cheese pizza that tasted so much like paradise that I didn&amp;rsquo;t even regret the inflammation and discomfort I had from it the next two days!</description></item><item><title>A Smashing Valentine's Day</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-smashing-valentines-day/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-smashing-valentines-day/</guid><description>This Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day is going to be a little more low-key for us and we like it that way right now. :) However, low-key doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean we aren&amp;rsquo;t doing anything new or special! Because we want to continue keeping our marriage fresh, right?! We plan to do that by going back to our 90&amp;rsquo;s childhood and play on our Nintendo 64!!
Trevor has been playing Super Smash Brothers on the 64 with some of his friends and he realized how much he truly missed playing it!</description></item><item><title>Lock Your Love - Part 2</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/lock-your-love-part-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/lock-your-love-part-2/</guid><description>In the previous post, &amp;ldquo;Lock Your Love,&amp;rdquo; I shared this awesome gate found in St. George where you can symbolically protect your love by attaching a padlock to a gate or a bridge. Go read that post because it&amp;rsquo;s a neat idea! I thought more about how this idea reflects marriage and found some great symbolism I wanted to share.
Locked strongly into place My thoughts lingered on the lock itself, in that it&amp;rsquo;s nearly effortless to lock into place.</description></item><item><title>Lock Your Love - Part 1</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/lock-your-love-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/lock-your-love-part-1/</guid><description>*This post contains affiliate links.
I used to go to Dixie State University (it was Dixie State College when I went), so I lived down in good ole St. George, Utah! I loved it there so much. I could go on forever about why I love St. George but that would take all day! So I&amp;rsquo;m just going to share this one majorly awesome thing that came from living down there.</description></item><item><title>Newlywed Christmas Cards: Round Two</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/newlywed-christmas-cards-round-two/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/newlywed-christmas-cards-round-two/</guid><description>I did choose to send out Christmas cards again this year and man was it easier than my first attempt last year! This year I did a double-sided card so we could have a picture of us and a quick &amp;ldquo;happy holidays&amp;rdquo; message, but also have a back where we shared a picture from something special we did this year: we threw a Back to the Future party because I&amp;rsquo;m obsessed with BTTF!</description></item><item><title>5 Ways to Keep Christmas Gifts a Surprise From Your Spouse</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/5-ways-to-keep-christmas-gifts-a-surprise-from-your-spouse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/5-ways-to-keep-christmas-gifts-a-surprise-from-your-spouse/</guid><description>Have you ever had a hard time buying a gift for your spouse while keeping it a surprise? I personally have a problem with it just solely on the fact that I just can&amp;rsquo;t wait for them to enjoy what I got them! Well for this post I&amp;rsquo;m talking about keeping it a secret financially.
If you are like us and have openly shared finances, you probably struggle with getting gifts without your spouse knowing.</description></item><item><title>Be Thankful and Count the Blessings</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/be-thankful-and-count-the-blessings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/be-thankful-and-count-the-blessings/</guid><description>Isn&amp;rsquo;t it hard sometimes to be thankful in the midst of your trials? It&amp;rsquo;s not easy trying to see the positive in every situation. That&amp;rsquo;s why I felt like this new decor in our kitchen would be a helpful reminder to us that there is always something to be thankful, no matter what we experienced in the day! It helped even more to have pictures up representing things we are thankful for too.</description></item><item><title>The Pressures of Newlywed Bucket Lists</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-pressures-of-newlywed-bucket-lists/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-pressures-of-newlywed-bucket-lists/</guid><description>In case I haven&amp;rsquo;t said this a lot lately, I&amp;rsquo;m super excited to be graduating with my bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in WEEKS. Well, to celebrate, we&amp;rsquo;ve been talking/planning/deciding/not deciding on taking a graduation vacation :) And what I mean by that is we have had ideas of where we would love to vacation and then haven&amp;rsquo;t been sure about them, so we put it on hold until the next idea comes along.</description></item><item><title>Life is Sweet in The Belly of The Beast</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/life-is-sweet-in-the-belly-of-the-beast/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/life-is-sweet-in-the-belly-of-the-beast/</guid><description>This week&amp;rsquo;s lesson: you have to know the misery to know joy! The past six weeks have been kinda overwhelming for us. School has consumed much of my daily life and my weekends. And I think it took me two weeks to finally get motivated to do my homework and be a part of school because I was just feeling so burned out&amp;ndash; burned out from doing 4 semesters in a row and only having a week break before starting the fifth and FINAL one.</description></item><item><title>Complete Rather Than Compete</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/complete-rather-than-compete/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/complete-rather-than-compete/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m excited to say that this guy is starting a new job at DOMO tomorrow and I&amp;rsquo;m pretty proud of him! Getting this job is kind of a bittersweet story for us, and I want to share it because I think it&amp;rsquo;s something every marriage will face on some level.
&amp;ldquo;There is so much more of happiness to be had when we can rejoice in another&amp;rsquo;s successes and not just in our own.</description></item><item><title>Our First Year Being Homeowners</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/our-first-year-being-homeowners/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/our-first-year-being-homeowners/</guid><description>It was exactly one year ago today that we broke our bodies moving into our house! haha jk but seriously, we didn&amp;rsquo;t move from the couch and unpack anything for two straight days because we were so sore. The time and effort was all worth it though because we have a beautiful, put together home to show for it :)
And to think, it only took: 3 months to get a shower curtain in the guest bathroom 4 months to get actual blinds instead of the brown banner paper we had in every window&amp;hellip; tacky I know, it&amp;rsquo;s fine.</description></item><item><title>Celebrity Marriages vs. Other Marriages</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/celebrity-marriages-vs.-other-marriages/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/celebrity-marriages-vs.-other-marriages/</guid><description>I know we are all used to seeing celebrity couples splitting up, but gosh has anybody else noticed it&amp;rsquo;s been like one or two every week?! This happens all the time, sadly so I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect myself to post on this. However, I saw a headline that got me thinking about it more. The headline said, &amp;ldquo;First Ben and Jennifer, now Blake and Miranda? Is anyone else losing faith in marriage, too?</description></item><item><title>The Hunt Is Over</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-hunt-is-over/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-hunt-is-over/</guid><description>*This blog post contains affiliate links. Hi. Wedding shower fun here! Last weekend I threw my SIL a bridal shower and it was great! I literally spent two months planning and getting excited to do it because I had a fun idea that was unique to her and unique to bridal showers in general. She LOVES hunting, fishing, that outdoorsy stuff, AND perfectly enough &amp;mdash; her fiance loves all of that too!</description></item><item><title>The Little Victories</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-little-victories/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-little-victories/</guid><description>I have been thinking about the little milestones in marriage a lot lately. The anniversaries and growing families are great &amp;ndash; super awesome milestones! But I think it&amp;rsquo;s nice to honor those little things we do in marriage&amp;hellip; The &amp;ldquo;little victories&amp;rdquo; if you will!
The little victory I had when I wrote this was making a meal I have never made before, and slam dunkin&amp;rsquo; the &amp;ldquo;HONEY THIS TASTES SO GOOD!</description></item><item><title>The Iron: Part 2</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-iron-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-iron-part-2/</guid><description>Remember how I was so frustrated/annoyed/intimidated/scared of my iron? hahaha yeah so this started the very beginning of our marriage. It was actually my very first post, too! Basically, ironing was a stressful ordeal for me and became so much more difficult than it should have been. I was even more bugged about it because I felt like I NEEDED to ironing my husband&amp;rsquo;s dress shirts all the time, in order to be a good wife.</description></item><item><title>Why An Associate Degree Is a Big Deal To Me</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/why-an-associate-degree-is-a-big-deal-to-me/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/why-an-associate-degree-is-a-big-deal-to-me/</guid><description>This week my Associate in Science degree finally came in the mail! I practically earned it last summer, and then had to wait to apply for it in the fall, and then it got sent to the wrong address, haha. So I have had these proud feelings for 9 months, but finally got the paperwork to show for it ;) Believe it or not, my college career began in Fall 2009&amp;hellip; Over the past six years, I made important life decisions that took me all over Utah, and to three different universities&amp;hellip; haha.</description></item><item><title>Second Anniversary</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/second-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/second-anniversary/</guid><description>We celebrated our second anniversary this weekend, and it was just lovely. We stayed one night at the Anniversary Inn, enjoying the same room we spent our wedding night in. It was magical to have memories flood me from two years ago, and was just so relaxing to get away from the world for a little bit. On the way there we ate at Happy Sumo and it was just really chill, I loved it.</description></item><item><title>An OK Cliche</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/an-ok-cliche/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/an-ok-cliche/</guid><description>During a typical week day, there&amp;rsquo;s a time where my life becomes like an apron-wearing, oven-ready &amp;ldquo;50&amp;rsquo;s housewife cliché&amp;rdquo;. I love this time of the day.
Around 3:30 or 4 pm, my thoughts start to focus on the refrigerator, and pantry, where I figure out what nice meal I can make for us for dinner. Sometimes it feels kind of stressful because I want to make something yummy, fulfilling, and healthy for us, and I&amp;rsquo;m not always prepared as I could be.</description></item><item><title>The Difference a Picture Can Make</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-difference-a-picture-can-make/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-difference-a-picture-can-make/</guid><description>I didn&amp;rsquo;t realize how big of a deal it was to have family pictures up until now. I always thought people made too big of a deal over getting family portraits taken every year, and switching the pictures out in their home every time. While I love the idea of that, it&amp;rsquo;s not about having formal family photos to show off. To be honest, Trevor and I prefer the silly candid iPhone pictures we take, even in selfie form!</description></item><item><title>New Year's Resolutions: Married-Style</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/new-years-resolutions-married-style/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/new-years-resolutions-married-style/</guid><description>Our first married NYE&amp;rsquo;s in 2013, we went out to dinner to Red Lobster and had a four-course meal discussing our New Year&amp;rsquo;s resolutions. We had a great time enjoying good food, good company, and talking about the goals and desires of our heart. We decided this year we would continue that as a tradition every NYE! So this year we went out to Buffalo Wild Wings (one of our favs) and listed out to each other our plans for the new year, and it was great!</description></item><item><title>Newlywed Christmas Cards</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/newlywed-christmas-cards/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/newlywed-christmas-cards/</guid><description>We chose to send out Christmas cards for the first time this year, and this was our little insert. I meant to post this way before Christmas, but we had some technical difficulties on the back-end of our website. So even though Christmas has come and gone, we hope you can still appreciate our well-wishes to you for the holidays!
I’m not sure if a lot of you send out Christmas cards, but I want to share what we did for those of you thinking about doing it.</description></item><item><title>The Married Student Ward Experience</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-married-student-ward-experience/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-married-student-ward-experience/</guid><description>I have loved our married student ward here in Provo, and I am going to miss it dearly! I especially will miss the Sisters who have been in the ward, as they have influenced my life in many ways. I guess, this post is a goodbye letter to them, as well as an encouragement for those who are also in married student wards.
For those of you unfamiliar with what a &amp;ldquo;ward&amp;rdquo; is, it&amp;rsquo;s a way of referring to a local congregation within the LDS faith.</description></item><item><title>Our First Apartment</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/our-first-apartment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/our-first-apartment/</guid><description>Our little apartment is being emptied. All the pictures and artwork have been taken down from the walls, leaving them as blank as a piece of paper. Our couch has been sold, so movies are being watched in our bed now. The shelves have been cleared, and the drawers are empty. Clothes are in bags, appliances are wrapped up, and the random things are boxed up.. Well, pretty much everything is boxed up&amp;hellip; our life&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s all boxed up and ready to be put elsewhere.</description></item><item><title>Our House Story Part 2: You Can Learn a Lot in Four Days</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/our-house-story-part-2-you-can-learn-a-lot-in-four-days/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/our-house-story-part-2-you-can-learn-a-lot-in-four-days/</guid><description>If you read Part 1, you&amp;rsquo;ll know that we went into our appointment feeling worried about the huge price increase on the home plan we were interested in the most. We let them know we were very serious about this home, but that the price jump was going to be a deal-breaker for us. We asked the rep if there was anything they can do for us on that, since it happened literally overnight.</description></item><item><title>Our House Story Part 1: Timing is Everything</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/our-house-story-part-1-timing-is-everything/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/our-house-story-part-1-timing-is-everything/</guid><description>When we first started thinking about the idea of moving and buying a house, it was difficult to be fully invested in the idea because there were multiple factors that were up in the air that could alter that idea. It really felt like everything was about timing. We weren&amp;rsquo;t sure if the timing was right with me going back to school. We also weren&amp;rsquo;t sure if we should save up a little more, though we did already have a down payment.</description></item><item><title>Home is {insert cliche here}</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/home-is-insert-cliche-here/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/home-is-insert-cliche-here/</guid><description>Ready for these two exciting announcements?
We are moving! We bought a house! Yep. This just got real. It&amp;rsquo;s awesome yet crazy, and just a huge step in our lives but we are so excited to take that step! Though the idea of moving has been in the works for us for about five months, the opportunity with this specific house came up quick. And when I mean quick, I mean that we had three days to decide on it, haha.</description></item><item><title>The Thing About Provo</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-thing-about-provo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-thing-about-provo/</guid><description>We love living in Provo. There&amp;rsquo;s some great things about this area (Provo &amp;amp; Orem) that set it apart from other cities in Utah. The music scene has been great to be a part of, and has been the creator of some memorable date nights for us. Someone, somewhere nearby, for some inexpensive price is always playing, and they are usually pretty entertaining. I don&amp;rsquo;t know of any town that can do that, let alone, has enough talent to give birth to some great bands.</description></item><item><title>Starting Our Second Year</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/starting-our-second-year/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/starting-our-second-year/</guid><description>We are now on month 13 and I&amp;rsquo;m feeling grateful for where we are at. It is funny because this month I&amp;rsquo;ve suddenly felt like we gained a little bit more maturity with completing one year. Every year brings it&amp;rsquo;s certain experiences that allow us to learn and grow, so each year we&amp;rsquo;ll become just a little tinsy-tiny bit more wiser than the year before, and I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to it :) With that being said, I think it is important to look back at things we have learned.</description></item><item><title>One Year</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/one-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/one-year/</guid><description>Well, Trevor and I have now been married for one year! It&amp;rsquo;s an interesting feeling of happiness, pride, excitement, and weirdness at the same time&amp;hellip; if that makes any sense, haha. It is weird because of how quickly, yet slowly the year went by, and how different we are from a year ago! We were individuals that learned how to be one. We made plans, and some of those plans changed in unexpected ways.</description></item><item><title>Anniversary Gifts</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/anniversary-gifts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/anniversary-gifts/</guid><description>Our one year anniversary is coming up, and I am finding myself getting more excited about it each day! I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about how things were a year ago, and how far we have come since then. I have started looking back at our first year with such gratitude for the blessings that have come, and also for the trials that we have seen. And then I stumble upon all the cute things that made me fall in love with Trevor in the first place :) And that puts me in an instant twitterpated state of mind, haha.</description></item><item><title>The Easter Bunny</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-easter-bunny/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-easter-bunny/</guid><description>I remember reading an article last month on Huffington Post called, &amp;ldquo;Can We Bring The Holidays Down A Notch?&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s a Mom telling about the stress that she feels comes with Holidays while feeling pressure from other moms who seem to make each holiday bigger than the last. I&amp;rsquo;m not a mom with kids who sometimes need to be pampered with gifts on holidays, but as a newlywed, I can relate to feeling that pressure as well.</description></item><item><title>Not Too Cool for School</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/not-too-cool-for-school/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/not-too-cool-for-school/</guid><description>School. There&amp;rsquo;s so much importance that is stressed on getting an education, and going to school. It&amp;rsquo;s something that seems to be on every young-adult&amp;rsquo;s mind, because getting a degree is the next step after high school. It&amp;rsquo;s what everyone is doing, right? Well, not everyone.
It can be harder to accomplish this personal goal when married. The typical cycle around here, is that some couples find it best to have one spouse put school on hold to help support the other spouse&amp;rsquo;s education, with the hope that when they finish, the other spouse can go back and finish.</description></item><item><title>National Old Stuff Day</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/national-old-stuff-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/national-old-stuff-day/</guid><description>My twenty-second year was the best year of my life.
Yesterday, I told Trevor my feelings on this past birthday year, and how I think it&amp;rsquo;s going to be hard to top. He said, &amp;ldquo;Oh, don&amp;rsquo;t say that! We are together, so every year is going to get better and better.&amp;rdquo; I loved it. I think trials are bound to happen in the years ahead of us, because there is so much more that we get to, and need to experience.</description></item><item><title>Happy Opportunities</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/happy-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/happy-opportunities/</guid><description>This new year has already been eventful for us. We&amp;rsquo;ve been blessed with a few opportunities and things to look forward to, and now our lives are going in a different direction, and we are very happy about it.
Exciting news to share Trevor has chosen to start his career earlier than we planned, with a job offer from his dream job! He will be a Web Developer for The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints.</description></item><item><title>Winner of the Valentine's Giveaway</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/winner-of-the-valentines-giveaway/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/winner-of-the-valentines-giveaway/</guid><description>Thank you to everyone who entered the giveaway. We loved hearing everyone&amp;rsquo;s comments about how they try to make every day feel like Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day for their spouse! We have definitely taken notes from them. I hope everyone else goes back and reads each other&amp;rsquo;s comments to learn from them as well, because we all could use some advice, right?
The prize up for grabs is a $25 Cinemark movie theater gift card good towards a date night for Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day, or whenever you are feeling like taking out your sweetheart!</description></item><item><title>Valentine's Day Giveaway</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/valentines-day-giveaway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/valentines-day-giveaway/</guid><description>Every Day is Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day Somehow I really enjoy this holiday. I used to give little cheesy valentines to my friends and family, but I have since upgraded to legit 5x7 Cards that are decked out with cutesy embellishments and hand-written words of love. I also love seeing baked goods decorated in pinks and reds, with jimmy sprinkles all over! And furthermore, I love decorating baked goods myself&amp;ndash; heart shapes and everything!</description></item><item><title>Married at 22, And Proud of It</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/married-at-22-and-proud-of-it/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/married-at-22-and-proud-of-it/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m sure many of you have read that article circulating, called &amp;ldquo;23 Things to Do Instead of Getting Engaged Before You&amp;rsquo;re 23.&amp;rdquo; If you haven&amp;rsquo;t read it, you might find it interesting. (Please note that the article in the link contains explicit words.) So many opinions can be formed about this girl&amp;rsquo;s views, and many opinions have already been mentioned. In having a website focused on strengthening marriage, as well as helping the world understand the beauty of marriage, we couldn&amp;rsquo;t let our opinion go unheard.</description></item><item><title>365 Days of Love</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/365-days-of-love/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/365-days-of-love/</guid><description>This was how our year of 2013 was well-spent. [caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_1860&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;550&amp;rdquo;] 67 dates.
348 days spent together.
1863 laughs.
32 special songs shared.
1.7 million kisses. (give or take a few)
And 1 especially blissful day, when we became eternal best friends.[/caption]
Happy New Year everyone! We are so excited to begin this new year together, but 2013 was a wonderful year!
When I think back on all that we did, I can&amp;rsquo;t help but feel undeniably happy.</description></item><item><title>New And Improved Website</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/new-and-improved-website/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/new-and-improved-website/</guid><description>Hi, Freshly Married friends! You probably noticed that we have been gone for a while. Yes, we were with family. Yes, we were partying it up with Christmas and the New Year and what not&amp;hellip;but we were also working on this amazingly awesome new website! Wooo hooo! We hope you like it.
Along with the website updates, we created a new email list and social media accounts. Basically, to sum everything up, we are trying to make Freshly Married a better resource to help strengthen marriages.</description></item><item><title>A Traditional Christmas</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-traditional-christmas/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-traditional-christmas/</guid><description>It’s been said that this is the most wonderful time of the year. And other than this freezing cold weather we have been having, it sure feels true to me!
This seems to be the best Christmas season I’ve ever had. The first reason is because I get to experience it married to the love of my life, who automatically makes things the best. :) The second reason is because I feel a special kind of excitement for the many “firsts” and new traditions that we get to have.</description></item><item><title>Six Month Anniversary - Let's Commemorate Something</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/six-month-anniversary-lets-commemorate-something/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/six-month-anniversary-lets-commemorate-something/</guid><description>Trevor laughs at all the little moments in our relationship I try to commemorate, or that I feel the need to commemorate. When he sees a bottle of sparkling cider in the cupboard, I think he traces his memories to find out what moment I&amp;rsquo;m wanting to make a toast about with it (haha). Well, today is our six month anniversary, so naturally, I pulled out a bottle to celebrate over dinner.</description></item><item><title>LDS Weddings 101: Our Wedding Day</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/lds-weddings-101-our-wedding-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/lds-weddings-101-our-wedding-day/</guid><description>The sealing The best and most important part was done first thing in the morning: Get married to my best friend! After that, the mishaps don’t matter, because you are happy as can be!
Photography Pictures were taken with family and friends on the temple grounds, and afterwards, Trevor and I spent about an hour taking pictures just us and the photographer. I know many people do groomals before-hand, so that the wedding day isn’t rushed.</description></item><item><title>LDS Weddings 101: The Planning</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/lds-weddings-101-the-planning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/lds-weddings-101-the-planning/</guid><description>I would like to start out, by saying how much I loved my wedding day. From the Groom to the ceremony; to the decorations to the guests; and from the food to the fun, I loved it all! Of course, the day had a few blips, but that is inevitable! What it all came down to, was that I had just married the most perfect man for me, and we were celebrating that fact with people who loved and supported us.</description></item><item><title>The Three Week Milestone</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-three-week-milestone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-three-week-milestone/</guid><description>In the first three weeks of being married, I learned: The difference between wants and needs. Showing your love can sometimes be more important than saying it. Selfishness will never prosper in a partnership. Cuddling can fix sooooo many things!</description></item><item><title>Marriage Is The Best</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/marriage-is-the-best/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/marriage-is-the-best/</guid><description>We were recently married in the Latter-Day Saint temple. We wanted to share this experience with you - from our engagement to our lives now&amp;hellip;post-marriage. We hope you enjoy the words of the bride (amy) and the groom (trevor):
This post has 2 parts: The bride&amp;rsquo;s perspective, and the groom&amp;rsquo;s perspective!
The Groom Hello. I&amp;rsquo;m Trevor I&amp;rsquo;m Amy&amp;rsquo;s husband and I wanted to share my side of the story too :)</description></item><item><title>My Best Friend's Wedding(s)</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/my-best-friends-weddings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/my-best-friends-weddings/</guid><description>Well, more like, the best friends before we met our spouses. Saturday was Trevor&amp;rsquo;s (before me) best friend&amp;rsquo;s wedding. It was a beautiful, yet hot, day full of love and happiness for them. It was a long-awaited day for them, especially since we both started dating within a week of each other, and were engaged about the same time. It was so hard for those boys! They were so in love with us and they just kept waiting until we fully came around!</description></item></channel></rss>