<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>friendship on Freshly Married</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/tags/friendship/</link><description>Recent content in friendship on Freshly Married</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://freshlymarried.github.io/tags/friendship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>10 Tips to Help Your Marriage Emotionally Survive COVID-19</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/10-tips-to-help-your-marriage-emotionally-survive-covid-19/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/10-tips-to-help-your-marriage-emotionally-survive-covid-19/</guid><description>Seems weird to wish everyone a happy quarantine/lockdown, but these are the times we live in right now! It seems everyone is affected one way or another from the COVID-19 global pandemic. Some people are affected financially with job loss or revenue. Some people are affected with loss of loved ones or even just the loss of a social life. Some people are missing out on important milestones and celebrated events like weddings and even prom.</description></item><item><title>Bringing More Creativity to Your Relationship</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/bringing-more-creativity-to-your-relationship/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/bringing-more-creativity-to-your-relationship/</guid><description>**This post contains affiliate links. This means, if you make a purchase through any of these links, we’ll receive a small portion of your purchase at no extra cost to you. Thank you for supporting the brands that support Freshly Married!
Have you ever thought about creativity in your relationship? Hearing that might have some of you thinking, “Uh-oh… I’m not artsy or crafty whatsoever! How is this going to apply to me?</description></item><item><title>Gender Reveal!</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/gender-reveal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/gender-reveal/</guid><description>Everything about this pregnancy has been super exciting, not just for us but for our family and friends. I mean, it took us so much to finally get here, but we also get to experience the rare situation of twins! It&amp;rsquo;s also my in-laws&amp;rsquo; first grandbaby so it&amp;rsquo;s ALL very exciting for them.
So of course, we did a gender reveal party to share the sex of our identical twins with our family!</description></item><item><title>6 Questions to Help You Dream Together</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/6-questions-to-help-you-dream-together/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/6-questions-to-help-you-dream-together/</guid><description>**This post contains affiliate links. This means, if you make a purchase through any of these links, we&amp;rsquo;ll receive a small portion of your purchase at no extra cost to you. Thank you for supporting the brands that support Freshly Married!
The idea of sharing your hopes and dreams as individuals and as a couple is so meaningful to a relationship! There are so many positives it brings to your life because it’s a very hopeful concept.</description></item><item><title>My Words of The Year</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/my-words-of-the-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/my-words-of-the-year/</guid><description>Now that the secret is out that I’m pregnant with twins I can finally share my words of the year because it has everything to do with them. :) I say WORDS because I think it&amp;rsquo;s important to have a goal in mind for you as an individual, and then a goal in mind for your marriage. However you like to do your goals, whether by choosing a specific word to inspire you, a vision board, or simply writing down the goal in a sentence, make sure you are considering how you can strengthen your marriage.</description></item><item><title>#TableTalk -- Savory Dinner Conversations for Two</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/tabletalk-savory-dinner-conversations-for-two/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/tabletalk-savory-dinner-conversations-for-two/</guid><description>***This article contains affiliate links so if you purchase, I make a small percentage of that.
How many times do we eat dinner together at home in front of the television, without saying much to each other? We are pretty good at having conversations, but I can&amp;rsquo;t count how many times we&amp;rsquo;ve still done this. :) It&amp;rsquo;s easy to do when we just have the two of us, and we just want to escape from the tasks and stress of the day.</description></item><item><title>50 Gift Ideas for Your Spouse</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/50-gift-ideas-for-your-spouse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/50-gift-ideas-for-your-spouse/</guid><description>Every birthday, Christmas, Valentine’s Day, and wedding anniversary, I find myself googling thoughtful gift ideas that I can buy or make for my spouse. The same thing happens when I want to get a “just because” gift for him, or create a special date night for us. Add these up and we’ve got AT LEAST 5 times throughout the year searching for gift ideas.
Over the past few years, I have been keeping track of some awesome finds that interest me or my spouse, and I think most spouses would love too.</description></item><item><title>Why Your Spouse Won't Be Your Everything</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/why-your-spouse-wont-be-your-everything/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/why-your-spouse-wont-be-your-everything/</guid><description>I was watching an awesome TED talk from Belgian Psychotherapist, Esther Perel about desire in committed relationships. Specifically talking about having more desire and passion for intimacy. But she mentioned some REALLY great points that completely resonated with me, and I think they will with you too.
She talks about how as humans we have two fundamental human needs that conflict with each other when we are in a committed relationship.</description></item><item><title>Unboxing Video: "Blind Date" from Date Night In</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/unboxing-video-blind-date-from-date-night-in/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/unboxing-video-blind-date-from-date-night-in/</guid><description>Date boxes have been a new thing the past few years, and I think are recently gaining more traction for couples, especially those with busy lives. Last year my husband and I experimented with date boxes to see what they are all about, and to see if they would give us added fun in our marriage :)
I wrote an article on how date boxes work, so if you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar with the concept, check that out.</description></item><item><title>A Joyful Marriage - Week 36</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-joyful-marriage-week-36/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-joyful-marriage-week-36/</guid><description>This joy is going to AGAIN sound familiar&amp;hellip; trying new things together, or just things that we grew up doing but haven&amp;rsquo;t done since we&amp;rsquo;ve been together.
We went to a little Idaho getaway with family this weekend and had a blast doing a whole bunch of outdoorsy adventurous things we haven&amp;rsquo;t yet experienced together, like riding on four-wheelers,fishing and shooting. It&amp;rsquo;s weird that in our 5 years of being together, 4 years of that in marriage, we haven&amp;rsquo;t done these things yet, even though both of our families are outdoor sports adventurists.</description></item><item><title>4 Mistakes We Make When a Friend’s Marriage is Struggling</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/4-mistakes-we-make-when-a-friends-marriage-is-struggling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/4-mistakes-we-make-when-a-friends-marriage-is-struggling/</guid><description>It’s not easy to see your friends go through hard struggles, especially when it comes to such an important relationship like marriage. It’s also not easy to be the confidant, the person they choose to share their marital struggles with. Though I think you should try avoiding involving your friends in the personal details of your marriage, it’s a reality that friends will confide in you and you will confide in them.</description></item><item><title>Crated With Love - Date Box Review</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/crated-with-love-date-box-review/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/crated-with-love-date-box-review/</guid><description>My husband and I tried out different date boxes to give you an idea of what each one offers! This blog post is sharing our experiences with the &amp;ldquo;Crated With Love&amp;rdquo; date box company, giving you better insight into what their boxes are like. If you are unfamiliar with date boxes in general, read this previous blog post explaining everything about them - what they are, as well as the pros and cons.</description></item><item><title>Date Night In - Date Box Review</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/date-night-in-date-box-review/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/date-night-in-date-box-review/</guid><description>My husband and I tried out different date boxes to give you an idea of what each one offers! This blog post is sharing our experiences with the &amp;ldquo;Date Night In&amp;rdquo; date box company, giving you better insight into what their boxes are like. If you are unfamiliar with date boxes in general, read this previous blog post explaining everything about them - what they are, as well as the pros and cons.</description></item><item><title>Datelivery - Date Box Review</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/datelivery-date-box-review/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/datelivery-date-box-review/</guid><description>My husband and I tried out different date boxes to give you an idea of what each one offers! This blog post is sharing our experiences with the &amp;ldquo;Datelivery&amp;rdquo; date box company, giving you better insight into what their boxes are like. If you are unfamiliar with date boxes in general, read this previous blog post explaining everything about them - what they are, as well as the pros and cons.</description></item><item><title>100 Conversational Questions to Ask Your Spouse</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/100-conversational-questions-to-ask-your-spouse/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/100-conversational-questions-to-ask-your-spouse/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all been there You&amp;rsquo;re on a much-needed date night out, away from work, home, and the kids (if you have them). Whatever the activity you&amp;rsquo;re doing, there is time for conversations to happen and somehow the conversation ends up being any or all of the following scenarios:
Talking too much business stuff - the kids’ schedules, work stress, etc. Not knowing what to talk about, especially if you think you know everything about each other already Bringing up issues that start an argument I think we’ve all found ourselves in one of these situations on our date nights before.</description></item><item><title>Same Old Dates</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/same-old-dates/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/same-old-dates/</guid><description>THE SPECIAL OCCASION PRESSURES The night before Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day, we were talking about our holiday plans and my husband voiced to me that he has spent hours over the past few weeks trying to figure out a special activity for us to do for Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day that wasn&amp;rsquo;t something we had already done or that feels &amp;ldquo;same ole, same ole&amp;rdquo; like going to the movies. We even have a STRONG bucket list of so many more date night activities to try, but sometimes those ideas don&amp;rsquo;t work well with the season or other facts.</description></item><item><title>40 Two-Player Games to Play With Your Spouse</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/40-two-player-games-to-play-with-your-spouse/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/40-two-player-games-to-play-with-your-spouse/</guid><description>I LOVE PLAYING GAMES!!! They are just my jam. I get so excited when we get together with friends or family who want to play games because we don&amp;rsquo;t get to play those 3+ player games at home! Over the past four years together, we have managed to find some two-player games to play at home, but we get bored of them real quick. Since every couple needs to have some games to turn to, especially in the winter time, I figured I would make one big list for us all!</description></item><item><title>#freshfridays Quote: Branches vs. Roots</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/freshfridays-quote-branches-vs-roots/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/freshfridays-quote-branches-vs-roots/</guid><description>This quote below is great to remember in times of disconnection and conflict. We try to look on their surface for any emotion to provide us with answers, but what&amp;rsquo;s showing on the outside might not be how they actually feel or think.
You may think &amp;ldquo;He looks like he could care less right now! He&amp;rsquo;s stone-cold to me and doesn&amp;rsquo;t care about a resolution OR ME!&amp;rdquo; That might be what it looks like on the surface.</description></item><item><title>3 Ways to Keep Video Gaming From Harming Your Marriage</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/3-ways-to-keep-video-gaming-from-harming-your-marriage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/3-ways-to-keep-video-gaming-from-harming-your-marriage/</guid><description>[sc name=&amp;ldquo;soundcloud&amp;rdquo; id=&amp;ldquo;282755491&amp;rdquo; ]
Back in the dating life, I knew a few girls who would shy away from dating guys who played video games, simply because they instantly thought of it associated with a lazy, preoccupied husband. I have to admit that I dated a guy who played video games and at times I felt second to him because of it. So I can see where they got their judgements.</description></item><item><title>Object Lessons: The Marriage Recipe</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/object-lessons-the-marriage-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/object-lessons-the-marriage-recipe/</guid><description>Watch the video, then proceed to the rest of the post below :)
[sc name=&amp;ldquo;youtube&amp;rdquo; id=&amp;ldquo;BLpKabyYfds&amp;rdquo; ]
Making your own marriage recipe So you have your ingredients list above, and now you need the directions to follow, but where do you find those directions to follow? 3 ways you find those directions:
You study and learn through credible books, classes, and advice from others. You pull from your past relationship experiences of what worked and what didn&amp;rsquo;t work.</description></item><item><title>6 Ways to Prioritize Your Spouse</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/6-ways-to-prioritize-your-spouse/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/6-ways-to-prioritize-your-spouse/</guid><description>A reader asked what I would suggest as ways to prioritize your spouse, and I decided to put all that information in a post because my reply is too big for a comment box! haha. So here&amp;rsquo;s my reply to my previous post: &amp;ldquo;Prioritizing My Spouse.&amp;rdquo;
The idea of growing apart happens gradually over time. When you think about it, there will always be sudden situations that come up where you do need to be there for your kids over your spouse, but I think the problem starts when this is happening frequently.</description></item><item><title>The Married Journal</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-married-journal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-married-journal/</guid><description>I love being right in the middle of a memorable moment when a certain kind of happiness overcomes me, and I can’t help but think, “I will never forget this.” Those moments are deemed “memorable” for whatever reason, and can stay in our hearts forever. As much as we wish they can be replayed over and over, they can’t be; unless you have a time machine in the form of a flying DeLorean, and your name is Doctor Emmett Brown.</description></item><item><title>First Big Vacation</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/first-big-vacation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/first-big-vacation/</guid><description>So I&amp;rsquo;m finally sharing our beautiful trip to Hawaii we took in May! Two phrases I remember saying multiple times out loud and in mind are: &amp;ldquo;Bucket list item - CHECK!&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s another new thing I can say I tried!&amp;rdquo; I liked being able to make those little steps of progression in life, but doing them felt a million times more special and held more purpose getting to do them with my husband :)</description></item><item><title>The Three-Year Milestone</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-three-year-milestone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-three-year-milestone/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve been following along from the beginning, you&amp;rsquo;ll remember that I wrote about the following married milestones: being married for three weeks, and then three months. So naturally, I felt like doing a milestone post on being married for THREE YEARS! That&amp;rsquo;s such a small number, but I believe every year is an accomplishment! And we&amp;rsquo;ve experienced so much together in this short time, so it gets me excited about what we&amp;rsquo;ll experience at our 30-year mark!</description></item><item><title>The Best Reason to go on a Vacation</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-best-reason-to-go-on-a-vacation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-best-reason-to-go-on-a-vacation/</guid><description>For the last year, we have been looking into a big vacation for ourselves. We&amp;rsquo;ve done research to various places, planning, and multiple times were minutes away from actually booking a trip! Yet we haven&amp;rsquo;t pulled the trigger&amp;hellip; until now! We finally did it - we went to HAWAII! Some of you might be saying, &amp;ldquo;Going to Hawaii is this big for you guys?&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;We go on vacations all the time&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Well, it&amp;rsquo;s different for us, and because it&amp;rsquo;s not something we do often, it will be that much more special :)</description></item><item><title>Intentional Double Dating</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/intentional-double-dating/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/intentional-double-dating/</guid><description>*This post contains affiliate links.
Our time is very valuable as married couples, individuals, and parents. Weekends seem to be dispersed between your own events and obligations, family events, or just plain staying home on a Saturday night relaxing! If you got kids, throw in their games and activities, too. So when it comes to date night, it&amp;rsquo;s rare for some of us to find time for double dates, let alone our own dates!</description></item><item><title>Freshly Married Videos: Good Advice From Our Wedding Day</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/freshly-married-videos-good-advice-from-our-wedding-day/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/freshly-married-videos-good-advice-from-our-wedding-day/</guid><description>So here&amp;rsquo;s that part two video about the marriage advice we received on our wedding day! The first video was me going through pieces of &amp;ldquo;bad&amp;rdquo; (cliche, not the best to follow) advice and why I think it&amp;rsquo;s not the best to follow. For this video, however, I wanted to keep it more positive and focused on all the GOOD advice we received on our wedding day because there truly were some great things said to us that stuck with us!</description></item><item><title>Freshly Married Videos: Bad Marriage Advice From Our Wedding Day</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/freshly-married-videos-bad-marriage-advice-from-our-wedding-day/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/freshly-married-videos-bad-marriage-advice-from-our-wedding-day/</guid><description>FRESHLY MARRIED IS NOW ON YOUTUBE!!! Click on This button below to subscribe! I was feeling like I needed to be doing videos as another form of helping couples strengthen their marriage because we all learn in different ways.I think this is also a great opportunity for my personality to come out a little more, which can help our relationship feel more personable :) I&amp;rsquo;m all about relating to others because it allows you to better understand them and trust them.</description></item><item><title>Reaching Your Health Goals: Together or Individually?</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/reaching-your-health-goals-together-or-individually/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/reaching-your-health-goals-together-or-individually/</guid><description>This week I asked how couples get their exercise - do they work out together or individually, and why. The reason I asked is because this is something my husband and I have been trying to figure out for a while now! I&amp;rsquo;ve seen many couples do workouts together, or go on the same diets. I think it&amp;rsquo;s cool to have it be something you can do together because you get healthy while spending time together, you can encourage each other, and it can be convenient to eat the same meals.</description></item><item><title>Being a Married College Student</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/being-a-married-college-student/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/being-a-married-college-student/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m grateful that I was able to experience college being both single, and then married. In the beginning I was doing the college thing for the experience and learning, but finishing college as a married woman for the last few semesters was for more than that. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t just doing it for me anymore.
The Single College Life People tend to think that it&amp;rsquo;s best to go through college being single, or at least not yet married.</description></item><item><title>If You Haven't Been On a Date in Awhile...</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/if-you-havent-been-on-a-date-in-awhile/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/if-you-havent-been-on-a-date-in-awhile/</guid><description>To the couples who haven&amp;rsquo;t gone on a date in awhile:
GO ON A DATE! I know I say this a lot, and I don&amp;rsquo;t want to come off as annoying, judge-y or insensitive when I write this post. Life can be tough and in those tough times, we tend to put this incredibly important relationship of ours on the back-burner. It also happens when life is busy. For whatever the reason, these situations start to take precedence over something that is so essential to a relationship.</description></item><item><title>Stop Rolling Your Eyes</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/stop-rolling-your-eyes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/stop-rolling-your-eyes/</guid><description>To the older couple staring at us kissing in line, stop rolling your eyes about it.
To the people sick of listening to proposal stories, stop rolling your eyes about it.
To the people who joke about my husband and I being prom dates because we sometimes match his tie and my dress for church, stop rolling your eyes about it.
Why am I saying this? Because people tend to get annoyed of young love and it bugs me.</description></item><item><title>The Importance of Family Photos</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-importance-of-family-photos/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-importance-of-family-photos/</guid><description>As you have noticed, we got some new family photos done :) And I&amp;rsquo;m loving them! I had been watching my friend Nicky post so many amazing pictures she has taken of families and couples, and knew that she could give us the memorable photos we were looking for. Throughout the process I was so impressed with her professionalism, expertise, artistic eye, and even encouragement that we looked cute, haha. I just had a really great experience with her and wanted to mention that as I share a few photos from this shoot.</description></item><item><title>25</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/25-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/25-2/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve hit the quarter-life mark turning 25 last week and I feel the need to write about it. I have to say that I was not looking forward to this birthday just because the things I was wanting to do /to eat (but for reals!) I couldn&amp;rsquo;t have, or were out of reach. I thought that those things would make me happy. I have to admit that I totally cheated on my birthday and had two slices of cheese pizza that tasted so much like paradise that I didn&amp;rsquo;t even regret the inflammation and discomfort I had from it the next two days!</description></item><item><title>Stoplight Kisses</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/stoplight-kisses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/stoplight-kisses/</guid><description>We used to have a cute little tradition that we started when we were dating called, &amp;ldquo;Stoplight Kisses.&amp;rdquo; When we would drive together and approach a long stoplight, we would lean over and kiss each other :) Sometimes they were hurried kisses, and sometimes one of us kept our eyes open in case the light turned green, haha. But we enjoyed these little moments. Any excuse to kiss right?!
Over the past three years, I&amp;rsquo;m sorry to say we haven&amp;rsquo;t kept up with that tradition!</description></item><item><title>6 Ideas For Safeguarding Your Marriage on Social Media</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/6-ideas-for-safeguarding-your-marriage-on-social-media/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/6-ideas-for-safeguarding-your-marriage-on-social-media/</guid><description>Last year I wrote a series of posts on how social media can get the best of us and how it can affect our marriages. I now want to discuss another aspect of social media that can affect our marriages.
THINK ABOUT YOUR SOCIAL CONNECTIONS I didn&amp;rsquo;t think there was a problem having tons of friends when I first started facebook back in high school. It was neat to be able to connect, but then I realized how it can make me feel envious or inadequate when I spend a lot of time on it and am involved in other people&amp;rsquo;s lives so much.</description></item><item><title>Love Notes: The Lifelong Love Letter</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/love-notes-the-lifelong-love-letter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/love-notes-the-lifelong-love-letter/</guid><description>My husband and I have both mentioned in posts how much we enjoy giving and receiving love notes from each other. I really think there&amp;rsquo;s an awesome power that comes with love notes. Having a physical copy of how your spouse feels about you is something you can refer to in years to come, which makes it more special. Trevor and I used to write more to each other while we were dating, and I think it&amp;rsquo;s because we lived an hour away from each other.</description></item><item><title>A Smashing Valentine's Day</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-smashing-valentines-day/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-smashing-valentines-day/</guid><description>This Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day is going to be a little more low-key for us and we like it that way right now. :) However, low-key doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean we aren&amp;rsquo;t doing anything new or special! Because we want to continue keeping our marriage fresh, right?! We plan to do that by going back to our 90&amp;rsquo;s childhood and play on our Nintendo 64!!
Trevor has been playing Super Smash Brothers on the 64 with some of his friends and he realized how much he truly missed playing it!</description></item><item><title>Love Languages Part 1: Understanding</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/love-languages-part-1-understanding/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/love-languages-part-1-understanding/</guid><description>*This post contains affiliate links. I am a huge believer in love languages! Gary Chapman is most well-known for this idea in his book: &amp;ldquo;The Five Love Languages.&amp;rdquo; There are other interpretations when it comes to understanding how people feel loved but this seems to hit it on the head for me! I honestly could say I have a testimony on how important this concept is to marriages because I utilize it repeatedly in my marriage and in other relationships!</description></item><item><title>4000 Questions to Enhance Your Date Nights</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/4000-questions-to-enhance-your-date-nights/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/4000-questions-to-enhance-your-date-nights/</guid><description>**This post contains affiliate links. This means, if you make a purchase through any of these links, we’ll receive a small portion of your purchase at no extra cost to you. Thank you for supporting the brands that support Freshly Married!
For the past four or five months on our dates we have been trying to better focus our conversations on ourselves, rather than work, school, and other business. Trevor would think of questions or look up some to ask each other and it was fun.</description></item><item><title>The Six Stages of My Family Planning Journey</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-six-stages-of-my-family-planning-journey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-six-stages-of-my-family-planning-journey/</guid><description>If you are like me, you are at the point in your marriage where the idea of having children weighs more heavily on your mind. Whatever the reason for it, getting to this point has been an interesting journey, at least it has been for me! When we first got married the idea of starting a family was a simple goal for us: &amp;ldquo;Not for five years.&amp;rdquo; However as months and months have passed since then, I can tell you now that it&amp;rsquo;s actually not that simple, haha.</description></item><item><title>Phone-a-Friend</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/phone-a-friend/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/phone-a-friend/</guid><description>I just read an article about a national study that found 73% of Americans have given advice to a friend or family member about their relationships. Source is at the bottom because I don&amp;rsquo;t want to bore you like a class lecture. However, I do want to address this important role of being a confidant to others on their relationships, because these people can be a very influential lifeline to your marriage success, whether it&amp;rsquo;s positive or negative.</description></item><item><title>Fire-Wife Life</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/fire-wife-life/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/fire-wife-life/</guid><description>As we all know, there are different kinds of marital experiences! A few that I have received better insight into this year are marriages that have a spouse serving in the armed forces, police work, firefighters, or EMT&amp;rsquo;s. Because of their job description and the sacrifice they make to help protect us, they face different challenges in their marriages than other couples might face. Since I do not have first-hand experience in this area, I asked someone who has absolute experience in this to help us understand better.</description></item><item><title>The Pressures of Newlywed Bucket Lists</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-pressures-of-newlywed-bucket-lists/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-pressures-of-newlywed-bucket-lists/</guid><description>In case I haven&amp;rsquo;t said this a lot lately, I&amp;rsquo;m super excited to be graduating with my bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in WEEKS. Well, to celebrate, we&amp;rsquo;ve been talking/planning/deciding/not deciding on taking a graduation vacation :) And what I mean by that is we have had ideas of where we would love to vacation and then haven&amp;rsquo;t been sure about them, so we put it on hold until the next idea comes along.</description></item><item><title>Monday Morning Pick-Me-Ups</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/monday-morning-pick-me-ups/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/monday-morning-pick-me-ups/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m so glad we happened to get a blooper photo of me actually picking my husband up because it worked perfectly for this ;)
Mondays can be hard, huh? It&amp;rsquo;s beginning another week of the daily grind, wishing you could go back to Friday :) What helps us get by on these days where we are lagging? Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s a funny video on youtube. Other times it&amp;rsquo;s a diet coke or brownie.</description></item><item><title>The Power of Kindness</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-power-of-kindness/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-power-of-kindness/</guid><description>We all know that being kind can change someone&amp;rsquo;s entire day around, or maybe someone&amp;rsquo;s act of kindness has changed YOUR entire day. Kindness is so powerful, if you didn&amp;rsquo;t know that already! Throughout my marriage I&amp;rsquo;ve definitely been shown and taught how powerful it can be.
When Trevor and I first experienced tiffs with each other, our process of being upset and also working through it was something new to me.</description></item><item><title>Life is Sweet in The Belly of The Beast</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/life-is-sweet-in-the-belly-of-the-beast/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/life-is-sweet-in-the-belly-of-the-beast/</guid><description>This week&amp;rsquo;s lesson: you have to know the misery to know joy! The past six weeks have been kinda overwhelming for us. School has consumed much of my daily life and my weekends. And I think it took me two weeks to finally get motivated to do my homework and be a part of school because I was just feeling so burned out&amp;ndash; burned out from doing 4 semesters in a row and only having a week break before starting the fifth and FINAL one.</description></item><item><title>The Date Night Bucket List</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-date-night-bucket-list/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-date-night-bucket-list/</guid><description>*This post contains affiliate links.
On our first date, Trevor and I started talking about some things we like to do, and we found most of them we had in common (of course!) Since he had recently come home from serving an Latter-Day Saint mission, I started suggesting some of the movies he should watch and music to listen to that came out while he was gone. It started as that, and then somehow it turned into things that we were possibly going to do together&amp;hellip; :) So being the list people that we are, Trevor pulled out his phone and created a google doc, listing these things to do.</description></item><item><title>My Struggle With Social Media: Part 3</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/my-struggle-with-social-media-part-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/my-struggle-with-social-media-part-3/</guid><description>This is the last post in a series of three posts on this subject. It would be beneficial to read part 1 and part 2 before or after reading this post :)
How social media has affected my marriage Trevor and I differ on our level of social interaction. I have a stronger need for it than he does, and it’s OK :)Being different in this way set a good example to me, that I’m grateful for.</description></item><item><title>My Struggle With Social Media: Part 2</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/my-struggle-with-social-media-part-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/my-struggle-with-social-media-part-2/</guid><description>This is part 2 of 3. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t read part 1 yet, reading it would probably be to your benefit. :)
All the world&amp;rsquo;s a stage I think each of us are on a stage. We give a public presentation of ourselves to an audience &amp;ndash; the people walking by us on the streets, our co-workers, friends, family, and our virtual friends on social media. When we go out on stage, we pick the parts of ourselves that we want people to see.</description></item><item><title>My Struggle With Social Media: Part 1</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/my-struggle-with-social-media-part-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/my-struggle-with-social-media-part-1/</guid><description>From about September to December, I really struggled emotionally with social media. I fell into some common pitfalls of comparing my life to other people&amp;rsquo;s lives, questioning how &amp;ldquo;real&amp;rdquo; people were, and spending more time being involved in it than I should have (though I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t say I was addicted). These things were lowering my self-worth, and making me feel ungrateful. I snapped out of this phase and realized some important things that have made me and my marriage happier.</description></item><item><title>Loving at Arms-Length</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/loving-at-arms-length/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/loving-at-arms-length/</guid><description>I attended a women&amp;rsquo;s conference with my mom a few weeks ago and I was inspired by one of the speakers who talked about &amp;ldquo;loving at arms-length.&amp;rdquo; It was actually Dawn Armstrong, the mother of the missionary from the movie, &amp;ldquo;Meet the Mormons.&amp;rdquo; She talked about how she has a lot of love for so many people; sometimes people who randomly come along. Her love for people grew ten fold when she stopped loving at arms-length, and instead pulled them in tight and gave them a hug.</description></item><item><title>Marriage is like a hiking trip</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/marriage-is-like-a-hiking-trip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/marriage-is-like-a-hiking-trip/</guid><description>Click the play button to LISTEN to this blog post!
[sc name=&amp;ldquo;soundcloud&amp;rdquo; id=&amp;ldquo;273872657&amp;rdquo; ]
Back in college I had to do an assignment relating marriage and relationships to something. It could be an object or an action, we just had to explain why. I found a lot of similarities between hiking and marriage so I wrote all those down here for you! :)
It&amp;rsquo;s a crazy, fun, stressful, scary, beautiful adventure together.</description></item><item><title>The Honeymoon phase</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-honeymoon-phase/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-honeymoon-phase/</guid><description>When you think about a typical honeymoon (or look back on your own honeymoon), it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty great experience :) This picture is of us on our honeymoon to Park City; a.k.a Our best vacation ever! Honeymoons are full of fun, low-stress, and are fairly worry-free because the happiness of being together outweighs everything. That happiness continues on after the vacation is over. Hence, the &amp;ldquo;honeymoon phase&amp;rdquo; phrase, haha. It was such a simple time.</description></item><item><title>Do Your Best</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/do-your-best/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/do-your-best/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve totally been absent for a long time, I know. Sorry. I definitely have my reasons though. I love blogging and writing about aspects of married life that can be useful for people, but I think it&amp;rsquo;s important to take a step back from writing, and just enjoy those aspects of married life, instead.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been so busy the past few months. Though I enjoy being busy for the most part, I start to hate it when it is consistent and doesn&amp;rsquo;t come with a nice break.</description></item><item><title>Our First Apartment</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/our-first-apartment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/our-first-apartment/</guid><description>Our little apartment is being emptied. All the pictures and artwork have been taken down from the walls, leaving them as blank as a piece of paper. Our couch has been sold, so movies are being watched in our bed now. The shelves have been cleared, and the drawers are empty. Clothes are in bags, appliances are wrapped up, and the random things are boxed up.. Well, pretty much everything is boxed up&amp;hellip; our life&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s all boxed up and ready to be put elsewhere.</description></item><item><title>If Friends Were Flowers, I'd Pick You</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/if-friends-were-flowers-id-pick-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/if-friends-were-flowers-id-pick-you/</guid><description>Before I got married, I would hear things about how friendships change when a friend gets married. I heard that the girls nights disappear, and the friends stop calling each other. I heard that single friends think their married friend is too consumed in their husband to care about them, or that there&amp;rsquo;s no relating to each other anymore. I&amp;rsquo;ve also heard that the single friend feels like their married friend is always trying to set them, and it&amp;rsquo;s annoying to them.</description></item><item><title>The Music to Our Marriage</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-music-to-our-marriage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-music-to-our-marriage/</guid><description>Music is one of my favorite things that this life offers us. It has the power to inspire, to soften hearts, to change a mood, to make our bodies move, and ultimately, it can make us happy. My favorite thing about music, however, is its ability to preserve a memory, whether happy or sad, silly or annoying. I absolutely love that because of the many, MANY songs on my personal favorites list, every single one of them involves a memory&amp;hellip; Singing Backstreet Boys songs with my friend every drive I took from St.</description></item><item><title>Starting Our Second Year</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/starting-our-second-year/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/starting-our-second-year/</guid><description>We are now on month 13 and I&amp;rsquo;m feeling grateful for where we are at. It is funny because this month I&amp;rsquo;ve suddenly felt like we gained a little bit more maturity with completing one year. Every year brings it&amp;rsquo;s certain experiences that allow us to learn and grow, so each year we&amp;rsquo;ll become just a little tinsy-tiny bit more wiser than the year before, and I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to it :) With that being said, I think it is important to look back at things we have learned.</description></item><item><title>The Importance of Fun</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-importance-of-fun/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-importance-of-fun/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned our ideals on dating in marriage before, but we&amp;rsquo;ll mention it again: One of our expectations going into our marriage, was committing to have a date night each week. In looking back at our first year, I don&amp;rsquo;t think we missed a week. I know it&amp;rsquo;s so much easier for newlyweds to continue to date, and make time for dates, but that&amp;rsquo;s not an excuse to lack! No matter what stage of marriage you are in, I hope you ask each other out on fun dates still.</description></item><item><title>One Year</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/one-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/one-year/</guid><description>Well, Trevor and I have now been married for one year! It&amp;rsquo;s an interesting feeling of happiness, pride, excitement, and weirdness at the same time&amp;hellip; if that makes any sense, haha. It is weird because of how quickly, yet slowly the year went by, and how different we are from a year ago! We were individuals that learned how to be one. We made plans, and some of those plans changed in unexpected ways.</description></item><item><title>Anniversary Gifts</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/anniversary-gifts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/anniversary-gifts/</guid><description>Our one year anniversary is coming up, and I am finding myself getting more excited about it each day! I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about how things were a year ago, and how far we have come since then. I have started looking back at our first year with such gratitude for the blessings that have come, and also for the trials that we have seen. And then I stumble upon all the cute things that made me fall in love with Trevor in the first place :) And that puts me in an instant twitterpated state of mind, haha.</description></item><item><title>10 Things You Share in Marriage</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/sharing-is-caring/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/sharing-is-caring/</guid><description>Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been seeing how great it can be to share things with your spouse!
I had the reminder of this when I had consistent problems with my laptop computer that was junky, and Trevor suggested that I take over his personal macbook which was much much better than my PC. I&amp;rsquo;m sooooo grateful that I had someone else to rely on and offer to share with me, or else I would be without a computer and be stressed over finding the money to buy a new one!</description></item><item><title>Five Excuses</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/five-excuses/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/five-excuses/</guid><description>Trevor and I really enjoy having awesome TV shows to watch. We&amp;rsquo;ve already made that known in a previous post, where we spent most of March inside, while trading off being sick. There&amp;rsquo;s only so much you can do when you don&amp;rsquo;t feel well, right? But then what about the days that we feel great? Is it bad to enjoy a few episodes of a TV show? I mean, we all do it!</description></item><item><title>Stars and Butterflies</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/stars-and-butterflies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/stars-and-butterflies/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking a lot lately about the way our blog is viewed. I wonder how our experiences are responded to. I wonder if we&amp;rsquo;re too bold in some of our marriage ideals. And sometimes I wonder if our life comes off as this airy fantasy of what marriage really is like. After I have written something, I think back at the reasons we established this blog and ask myself if the particular post can be beneficial to our readers.</description></item><item><title>Couch Potatoes</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/couch-potatoes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/couch-potatoes/</guid><description>The past three weeks, Trevor and I have felt like we&amp;rsquo;ve been bums, couch potatoes, or whatever you call it. I am just finishing a cold I have had for the past 3 weeks, so I haven&amp;rsquo;t had much energy to workout, or do extra things beyond the necessary chores. I&amp;rsquo;ve mostly been tired, while Trevor has also been tired from some adjustments in his new job. While he loves it, his brain can be on overload sometimes.</description></item><item><title>365 Date Night Ideas</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/365-date-night-ideas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/365-date-night-ideas/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s be honest here. Every now and then, date nights can get a little routine doing the same things we usually do. This happens with us newlyweds too, believe it or not! So new ideas for date nights are good to have on those nights we feel like being spontaneous, or just wanting to do something different. Well, this is an idea that you can do any day of the week, in any season.</description></item><item><title>365 Days of Love</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/365-days-of-love/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/365-days-of-love/</guid><description>This was how our year of 2013 was well-spent. [caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_1860&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;550&amp;rdquo;] 67 dates.
348 days spent together.
1863 laughs.
32 special songs shared.
1.7 million kisses. (give or take a few)
And 1 especially blissful day, when we became eternal best friends.[/caption]
Happy New Year everyone! We are so excited to begin this new year together, but 2013 was a wonderful year!
When I think back on all that we did, I can&amp;rsquo;t help but feel undeniably happy.</description></item><item><title>The Yin and Yang Of Marriage</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/yinyang/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/yinyang/</guid><description>. [caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_1442&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;550&amp;rdquo;] This is a picture of our &amp;ldquo;hobby&amp;rdquo; room. One half of the picture is Amy&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;crafting corner&amp;rdquo; and the other half is my &amp;ldquo;coding corner&amp;rdquo;. Can you tell which side is Amy&amp;rsquo;s and which is mine? Uh&amp;hellip;let&amp;rsquo;s just say we have our own styles of organization&amp;hellip;hahaha :)[/caption]
Two IS better than one As you can see by this picture, we are very different in some ways; I am a perfectionist, soft-spoken, and nerdy.</description></item><item><title>You Are Perfect For Me</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/you-are-perfect-for-me/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/you-are-perfect-for-me/</guid><description>It’s November, which means most of us express extra gratitude for all of the blessings we have in our lives. As I’m very thankful for many things, the biggest blessing of all has been to have the love of my dear husband, Trevor.
I have several moments where I have so much gratitude for my spouse that I want to shout to the world, “I have the cutest husband!” However, I’m realizing that a better, more respectful thing to say, would be something along the lines of, “My husband is perfect for me” or “I’m so thankful for my husband.</description></item><item><title>Marriage Guidelines</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/marriage-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/marriage-guidelines/</guid><description>We love it when we come across marriage being talked about in the news. This article is something that was posted in the Deseret Newspaper in Salt Lake City, Utah, the other day, and I just wanted to share it.
Though I’m not sure that I agree with titling these “marriage commandments,” I do think it’s a great suggestion to compare them to the ten commandments we have been taught about through the gospel.</description></item><item><title>I Love Love Notes</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/i-love-love-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/i-love-love-notes/</guid><description>Amy and I can be a little goofy at times&amp;hellip; Actually, pretty much all the time :)
One of the goofy things we do is call each other &amp;ldquo;mine.&amp;rdquo; I came home to a note on the table today that said &amp;ldquo;mine.&amp;rdquo;
I love my wife. I am very thankful for the nice little notes that she leaves me around our apartment, on our bathroom mirror, on the fridge, through text messages, and through voicemails.</description></item><item><title>Top 10 Cheap Date Ideas</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/top-10-cheap-date-ideas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/top-10-cheap-date-ideas/</guid><description>Life is busy. There seems to be a never-ending list of stuff to fill our time with: work, school, errands, meal preparation, eating, sleeping, cleaning, exercise, church responsibilities, hobbies, appointments, social activities&amp;hellip; You get the point :)
Life can easily suffocate our schedules with endless commitments without leaving time for the ones we love most. To avoid this, my wife and I have set a goal to have an official date night at least once a week.</description></item><item><title>The Three Week Milestone</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-three-week-milestone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-three-week-milestone/</guid><description>In the first three weeks of being married, I learned: The difference between wants and needs. Showing your love can sometimes be more important than saying it. Selfishness will never prosper in a partnership. Cuddling can fix sooooo many things!</description></item><item><title>Buns, Bananas, And BBQ Chicken</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/buns-bananas-and-bbq-chicken/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/buns-bananas-and-bbq-chicken/</guid><description>My husband asks me out on a date every week. I KNOW RIGHT?! He really is the cutest husband. We had our partial date tonight in the park, having a picnic together. We grabbed the cute woven basket my cute mother-in-law gave us, and packed it full of buns, bananas, and BBQ chicken. It was lovely just sitting on the lush, green, grass, just eating, talking, and laughing. Trevor makes me giggle so much.</description></item></channel></rss>