<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>videos on Freshly Married</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/tags/videos/</link><description>Recent content in videos on Freshly Married</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://freshlymarried.com/tags/videos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Unboxing Video: "Blind Date" from Date Night In</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/unboxing-video-blind-date-from-date-night-in/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/unboxing-video-blind-date-from-date-night-in/</guid><description>Date boxes have been a new thing the past few years, and I think are recently gaining more traction for couples, especially those with busy lives. Last year my husband and I experimented with date boxes to see what they are all about, and to see if they would give us added fun in our marriage :)
I wrote an article on how date boxes work, so if you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar with the concept, check that out.</description></item><item><title>Prize Contest Celebrating Video Course!</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/prize-contest-celebrating-video-course/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/prize-contest-celebrating-video-course/</guid><description>The day before I came down with a nasty influenza I announced my video course: “How to Navigate Your Differences.” I also said that to celebrate I was going to do an awesome giveaway prize, and then… well the flu. Haha. And then it was my birthday so here we are now!
I just want to say that I have been so excited about this video course, because it&amp;rsquo;s so applicable for ALL marriages, no matter what stage you are in, or how deep your problems are!</description></item><item><title>Video: Books I Recommend For Sexual Intimacy Help</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/video-books-i-recommend-for-sexual-intimacy-help/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/video-books-i-recommend-for-sexual-intimacy-help/</guid><description>*This post contains affiliate links.
In March I did a live video on Facebook talking about different books on sexual intimacy that I would recommend to couples. There was great feedback on that video, and it sounded like several people appreciated it! So I wanted to make sure it was published on my website for others to access as well.
I only share three books in this video, but I think they are so great for helping couples enrich their sexual intimacy, whether this part of their marriage is heavily struggling, or they could just use some more insight.</description></item><item><title>A Unique and Easy Homemade Card</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/a-unique-and-easy-homemade-card/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/a-unique-and-easy-homemade-card/</guid><description>*This post contains affiliate links.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know a marriage that doesn&amp;rsquo;t give cards or love notes to each other for special occasions or even just for no reason at all! They can seem boring sometimes unless you get a funny one, or one that just has that unique factor&amp;hellip;
WELL. I&amp;rsquo;m going to show you how to make the EASIEST unique card you&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen! It folds and opens in a fun way, you can make at home with supplies you most likely have laying around, and you can embellish it however you want!</description></item><item><title>The Power of Empathy</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/the-power-of-empathy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/the-power-of-empathy/</guid><description>“The truth is, Rarely can a response make something better. What makes something better is connection.” - brene brown There&amp;rsquo;s this amazing video depicting empathy by Brene Brown that changed my life when I watched it. She talks about the difference between empathy and sympathy, the mistakes we tend to make when attempting to give empathy, and what we should be doing instead. It&amp;rsquo;s super short, yet super powerful! The animation helps you understand well, too.</description></item><item><title>Message In a Bottle</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/message-in-a-bottle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/message-in-a-bottle/</guid><description>Every anniversary we do a little something to celebrate our love! Like everyone else! haha. Some people choose to follow the theme of their year from that list of anniversary gifts here. I guess I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be told what to get my spouse because my spouse is unique! Our gift to each other was celebrating in Hawaii this year, but I wanted us to do something special there to mark the occasion.</description></item><item><title>The Sexy Dice Game</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/the-sexy-dice-game/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/the-sexy-dice-game/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share this idea with you guys because I think it&amp;rsquo;s a fun, EASY way to switch things up when it comes to your sex life!
For whatever reason, we all experience a hiatus of sexual intimacy at times. Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s because there are natural life transitions happening like having a baby, and other times you&amp;rsquo;re just needing a nudge to get back there. This game can be that nudge for your marriage!</description></item><item><title>Freshly Married Videos: Good Advice From Our Wedding Day</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/freshly-married-videos-good-advice-from-our-wedding-day/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/freshly-married-videos-good-advice-from-our-wedding-day/</guid><description>So here&amp;rsquo;s that part two video about the marriage advice we received on our wedding day! The first video was me going through pieces of &amp;ldquo;bad&amp;rdquo; (cliche, not the best to follow) advice and why I think it&amp;rsquo;s not the best to follow. For this video, however, I wanted to keep it more positive and focused on all the GOOD advice we received on our wedding day because there truly were some great things said to us that stuck with us!</description></item><item><title>Freshly Married Videos: Bad Marriage Advice From Our Wedding Day</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/freshly-married-videos-bad-marriage-advice-from-our-wedding-day/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/freshly-married-videos-bad-marriage-advice-from-our-wedding-day/</guid><description>FRESHLY MARRIED IS NOW ON YOUTUBE!!! Click on This button below to subscribe! I was feeling like I needed to be doing videos as another form of helping couples strengthen their marriage because we all learn in different ways.I think this is also a great opportunity for my personality to come out a little more, which can help our relationship feel more personable :) I&amp;rsquo;m all about relating to others because it allows you to better understand them and trust them.</description></item></channel></rss>