<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>home on Freshly Married</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/tags/home/</link><description>Recent content in home on Freshly Married</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://freshlymarried.com/tags/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>10 Tips to Help Your Marriage Emotionally Survive COVID-19</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/10-tips-to-help-your-marriage-emotionally-survive-covid-19/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/10-tips-to-help-your-marriage-emotionally-survive-covid-19/</guid><description>Seems weird to wish everyone a happy quarantine/lockdown, but these are the times we live in right now! It seems everyone is affected one way or another from the COVID-19 global pandemic. Some people are affected financially with job loss or revenue. Some people are affected with loss of loved ones or even just the loss of a social life. Some people are missing out on important milestones and celebrated events like weddings and even prom.</description></item><item><title>We Wash You A Happy Holiday!</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/we-wash-you-a-happy-holiday/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/we-wash-you-a-happy-holiday/</guid><description>This is for crafters AND non-crafters! *this blog post contains affiliate links through Amazon.
I&amp;rsquo;m a huge crafter and designed these gift tags for holiday gifts to some of our neighbors! I own a Cricut machine and have basically had it out all season long doing holiday stuff! I&amp;rsquo;ve recently ventured out exploring the other design tools it has in the program and using more than just the die-cutting option. YEP IT CAN WRITE.</description></item><item><title>Tips For Turning Your House Into a HOME</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/tips-for-turning-your-house-into-a-home/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/tips-for-turning-your-house-into-a-home/</guid><description>We have been in our house for almost 3 years, this August! It’s awesome to think back on how far we have come with putting it together, and making it feel like HOME.
I recently made an accomplishment with our house that I’m quite proud of &amp;ndash; I FINALLY finished decorating and furnishing our home! This event has made me think about the home furnishing and decorating process, what I liked that I did, and what I would do differently.</description></item></channel></rss>