<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>engagement on Freshly Married</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/tags/engagement/</link><description>Recent content in engagement on Freshly Married</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://freshlymarried.com/tags/engagement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Meant to be</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/meant-to-be/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/meant-to-be/</guid><description>Sharing time These pictures depict our lives before we &amp;ldquo;re-met&amp;rdquo; and started dating. Trevor was serving a Latter-Day Saint mission across the country while I was living at home, working at a craft store, and riding my scooter around trying to find myself again.
Though it was tough at times, these experiences were great for each of us to gain a new perspective and discover what we really wanted and what we were ready for&amp;hellip; each other.</description></item><item><title>The Future is as Bright as Your Faith</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/the-future-is-as-bright-as-your-faith/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/the-future-is-as-bright-as-your-faith/</guid><description>Three years ago I wrote this message to Trevor on the back of a picture quote as encouragement that we could do the long distance thing. (I&amp;rsquo;m sad we can&amp;rsquo;t find the original right now but glad I took a picture of the smeared message I wrote him!) The story behind this little message set a precedent for our relationship and it&amp;rsquo;s one I think every couple needs reminding of :)</description></item><item><title>Wedding Rings: More Than a Piece of Jewelry</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/wedding-rings-more-than-a-piece-of-jewelry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/wedding-rings-more-than-a-piece-of-jewelry/</guid><description>The day I was proposed to, the day I gave Trevor his wedding ring, and the day I got married to him were all days that showed me the meaning of a wedding ring. However, there was something else that happened this week where I realized the importance of a wedding ring again. And guess how it happened? While watching an episode of &amp;ldquo;Duck Dynasty&amp;rdquo; with my dad! hahaha. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain.</description></item><item><title>Because You're Worth It</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/because-youre-worth-it/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/because-youre-worth-it/</guid><description>Three years ago yesterday, Trevor asked me to be his wife! That was obviously a big moment for us, just as it is for any relationship. However, there were other things leading up to that moment that were also big in our relationship.
Story Time Two weeks before he proposed I had finally decided I was ready and wanted to move to be closer to him in Provo. This was a big deal for me because exactly a year prior to that I did the same thing&amp;ndash; move to Provo to be closer to a boy I was ready to marry.</description></item><item><title>The Hunt Is Over</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/the-hunt-is-over/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/the-hunt-is-over/</guid><description>*This blog post contains affiliate links. Hi. Wedding shower fun here! Last weekend I threw my SIL a bridal shower and it was great! I literally spent two months planning and getting excited to do it because I had a fun idea that was unique to her and unique to bridal showers in general. She LOVES hunting, fishing, that outdoorsy stuff, AND perfectly enough &amp;mdash; her fiance loves all of that too!</description></item><item><title>Married at 22, And Proud of It</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/married-at-22-and-proud-of-it/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/married-at-22-and-proud-of-it/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m sure many of you have read that article circulating, called &amp;ldquo;23 Things to Do Instead of Getting Engaged Before You&amp;rsquo;re 23.&amp;rdquo; If you haven&amp;rsquo;t read it, you might find it interesting. (Please note that the article in the link contains explicit words.) So many opinions can be formed about this girl&amp;rsquo;s views, and many opinions have already been mentioned. In having a website focused on strengthening marriage, as well as helping the world understand the beauty of marriage, we couldn&amp;rsquo;t let our opinion go unheard.</description></item><item><title>LDS Weddings 101: Our Wedding Day</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/lds-weddings-101-our-wedding-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/lds-weddings-101-our-wedding-day/</guid><description>The sealing The best and most important part was done first thing in the morning: Get married to my best friend! After that, the mishaps don’t matter, because you are happy as can be!
Photography Pictures were taken with family and friends on the temple grounds, and afterwards, Trevor and I spent about an hour taking pictures just us and the photographer. I know many people do groomals before-hand, so that the wedding day isn’t rushed.</description></item><item><title>LDS Weddings 101: The Planning</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/lds-weddings-101-the-planning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/lds-weddings-101-the-planning/</guid><description>I would like to start out, by saying how much I loved my wedding day. From the Groom to the ceremony; to the decorations to the guests; and from the food to the fun, I loved it all! Of course, the day had a few blips, but that is inevitable! What it all came down to, was that I had just married the most perfect man for me, and we were celebrating that fact with people who loved and supported us.</description></item><item><title>Marriage Is The Best</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/marriage-is-the-best/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/marriage-is-the-best/</guid><description>We were recently married in the Latter-Day Saint temple. We wanted to share this experience with you - from our engagement to our lives now&amp;hellip;post-marriage. We hope you enjoy the words of the bride (amy) and the groom (trevor):
This post has 2 parts: The bride&amp;rsquo;s perspective, and the groom&amp;rsquo;s perspective!
The Groom Hello. I&amp;rsquo;m Trevor I&amp;rsquo;m Amy&amp;rsquo;s husband and I wanted to share my side of the story too :)</description></item></channel></rss>