<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>religious on Freshly Married</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/tags/religious/</link><description>Recent content in religious on Freshly Married</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://freshlymarried.github.io/tags/religious/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>10 Tips for Going Through Fertility Treatments</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/10-tips-for-going-through-fertility-treatments/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/10-tips-for-going-through-fertility-treatments/</guid><description>A Little Bit of Our Story It took 2.5 years of trying to conceive (TTC) to get to this amazing point of being pregnant with identical twin boys! We feel absolutely blessed that we get two babies as a result of our hard work with the Utah Fertility Center. We did 3 timed intercourse cycles that required more and more pills and shots each time, but lead us to our first try at Intrauterine Insemination (IUI).</description></item><item><title>Decision-Making: The Three-Legged Race in Marriage</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/decision-making-the-three-legged-race-in-marriage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/decision-making-the-three-legged-race-in-marriage/</guid><description>The learning curve I think one of the biggest learning curves of newlyweds is decision-making. Of course, you had to make decisions before when you were dating and engaged, but it can be different because the stakes are different. And I think when a person is so smitten with someone, they are more likely to bend to the other person, haha.
The biggest difference when it comes to decision making in marriage is that you now have so many things you&amp;rsquo;re making decisions about, all involving and affecting the other person.</description></item><item><title>A Joyful Marriage - Week 48</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-joyful-marriage-week-48/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/a-joyful-marriage-week-48/</guid><description>I have about 4 more of these blog posts left of this #ajoyfulmarriage project, and I realized I haven&amp;rsquo;t shared about a major aspect of our marriage that brings us so much joy! It&amp;rsquo;s one that initially, I felt sad I hadn&amp;rsquo;t mentioned yet, but realized that this time of year brings it out even more, so it worked out saving it until now :)
Our spirituality brings us me so much joy in our marriage, and I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure my husband feels joy from it too.</description></item><item><title>Tips For Turning Your House Into a HOME</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/tips-for-turning-your-house-into-a-home/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/tips-for-turning-your-house-into-a-home/</guid><description>We have been in our house for almost 3 years, this August! It’s awesome to think back on how far we have come with putting it together, and making it feel like HOME.
I recently made an accomplishment with our house that I’m quite proud of &amp;ndash; I FINALLY finished decorating and furnishing our home! This event has made me think about the home furnishing and decorating process, what I liked that I did, and what I would do differently.</description></item><item><title>Pray Together, Stay Together</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/pray-together-stay-together/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/pray-together-stay-together/</guid><description>This is a common catchphrase in religions, even though it might not be a guarantee. While I believe praying is a powerful tool in marriage, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily guarantee a couple won&amp;rsquo;t get divorced. However, it does pull a large weight when it comes to feeling high marital quality.
I came across a recent article not too long ago from the Institute of Family Studies about how influential religion is in a couple&amp;rsquo;s marital satisfaction.</description></item><item><title>The Future is as Bright as Your Faith</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-future-is-as-bright-as-your-faith/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/the-future-is-as-bright-as-your-faith/</guid><description>Three years ago I wrote this message to Trevor on the back of a picture quote as encouragement that we could do the long distance thing. (I&amp;rsquo;m sad we can&amp;rsquo;t find the original right now but glad I took a picture of the smeared message I wrote him!) The story behind this little message set a precedent for our relationship and it&amp;rsquo;s one I think every couple needs reminding of :)</description></item><item><title>Religion Doesn't Guarantee A Lasting Marriage</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/religion-doesnt-guarantee-a-lasting-marriage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/religion-doesnt-guarantee-a-lasting-marriage/</guid><description>I was married in a Latter-Day Saint temple, where we believe allows your marriage to be eternal. However, simply having my marriage ceremony within my religion doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean I&amp;rsquo;m guaranteed to have a happy and healthy marriage! Believing you&amp;rsquo;ll have a forever marriage is different from actually creating one.
Principles to follow I firmly know that the principles taught in my Latter-Day Saint faith and many other faiths directly coincide with principles you should follow for a strong and happy marriage.</description></item><item><title>Christlike Attributes and My Marriage</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/christlike-attributes-and-my-marriage/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/christlike-attributes-and-my-marriage/</guid><description>I am religious and rely on God and his son, Jesus Christ, in nearly all aspects of my marriage. So I have been wanting to write about how religion influences my marriage. This week as I have been thinking about Easter and Jesus Christ&amp;rsquo;s Atonement, I have been focused on his actions from his time walking among us on earth: the examples he set of kindness, righteousness, and love. These qualities he displayed have become known as &amp;ldquo;Christlike attributes&amp;rdquo; and although there are many attributes that I could apply in my life, there are a few specifically that have been most applicable to my marriage that I wanted to point out.</description></item><item><title>Stoplight Kisses</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/stoplight-kisses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/stoplight-kisses/</guid><description>We used to have a cute little tradition that we started when we were dating called, &amp;ldquo;Stoplight Kisses.&amp;rdquo; When we would drive together and approach a long stoplight, we would lean over and kiss each other :) Sometimes they were hurried kisses, and sometimes one of us kept our eyes open in case the light turned green, haha. But we enjoyed these little moments. Any excuse to kiss right?!
Over the past three years, I&amp;rsquo;m sorry to say we haven&amp;rsquo;t kept up with that tradition!</description></item><item><title>Same-sex Marriage Doesn't Change My Traditional Marriage</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/same-sex-marriage-doesnt-change-my-traditional-marriage/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/same-sex-marriage-doesnt-change-my-traditional-marriage/</guid><description>Marriage has gone down in history this week with the legalization of same-sex marriages throughout the nation. The past few days I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about two things: 1) We are all human and we all have rights, despite our sexual orientation or religious beliefs. 2) How this is an opportune moment for us to increase our appreciation for marriage in general (traditional or non-traditional).
Recognizing the responsibilities Marriage is a big deal to me.</description></item><item><title>Sitting, Waiting, Wishing</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/sitting-waiting-wishing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/sitting-waiting-wishing/</guid><description>The word, &amp;ldquo;realistic&amp;rdquo; has been on my mind a lot lately: &amp;ldquo;Is this to-do list realistic?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Are my wants realistic right now?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Seriously, is this person&amp;rsquo;s life realistic?&amp;rdquo; These are just a few. I&amp;rsquo;ve had a realization that we need to be more honest and appear more realistic as a society, because that&amp;rsquo;s how people relate to each other. I have a hard time connecting with people who give a persona that life is perfect because we all know it&amp;rsquo;s not.</description></item><item><title>LDS Weddings 101: Our Wedding Day</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/lds-weddings-101-our-wedding-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/lds-weddings-101-our-wedding-day/</guid><description>The sealing The best and most important part was done first thing in the morning: Get married to my best friend! After that, the mishaps don’t matter, because you are happy as can be!
Photography Pictures were taken with family and friends on the temple grounds, and afterwards, Trevor and I spent about an hour taking pictures just us and the photographer. I know many people do groomals before-hand, so that the wedding day isn’t rushed.</description></item><item><title>LDS Weddings 101: The Planning</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/lds-weddings-101-the-planning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/lds-weddings-101-the-planning/</guid><description>I would like to start out, by saying how much I loved my wedding day. From the Groom to the ceremony; to the decorations to the guests; and from the food to the fun, I loved it all! Of course, the day had a few blips, but that is inevitable! What it all came down to, was that I had just married the most perfect man for me, and we were celebrating that fact with people who loved and supported us.</description></item><item><title>Note To Self</title><link>https://freshlymarried.github.io/note-to-self/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.github.io/note-to-self/</guid><description>Remember to cut the price tag off of your brand new blouse before you wear it to Sacrament meeting, in giving a talk at the pulpit, in front of a large congregation.
It’s fine. My husband slyly pulled it off after I sat back down.
Well, the time came, sooner than I had expected, that we were asked to speak in Sacrament meeting. To many of you, this may surprise you, but we actually enjoyed it.</description></item></channel></rss>