<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sex on Freshly Married</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/tags/sex/</link><description>Recent content in sex on Freshly Married</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://freshlymarried.com/tags/sex/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3 Areas of Sexual Intimacy Problems</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/3-areas-of-sexual-intimacy-problems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/3-areas-of-sexual-intimacy-problems/</guid><description>I don’t know any married couple that doesn’t struggle with sexual intimacy problems at SOME point in their marriage. While there are a variety of reasons why problems occur in this department, I believe there are three big areas that contribute to problems: safety, communication, and the influences around us.
SAFETY In order to have a healthy sexual communication between you and your spouse, there needs to be strong feelings of safety in the marriage.</description></item><item><title>Why Your Spouse Won't Be Your Everything</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/why-your-spouse-wont-be-your-everything/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/why-your-spouse-wont-be-your-everything/</guid><description>I was watching an awesome TED talk from Belgian Psychotherapist, Esther Perel about desire in committed relationships. Specifically talking about having more desire and passion for intimacy. But she mentioned some REALLY great points that completely resonated with me, and I think they will with you too.
She talks about how as humans we have two fundamental human needs that conflict with each other when we are in a committed relationship.</description></item><item><title>When One Spouse Wants Sex More Than The Other</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/when-one-spouse-wants-sex-more-than-the-other/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/when-one-spouse-wants-sex-more-than-the-other/</guid><description>*This post contains affiliate links.
A very common complaint among married couples, especially couples that have sexual intimacy problems, is that one spouse seems to want or enjoy sex more than their spouse does. This scenario is a difficult one to provide a one-size-fits-all answer to because there are two different perspectives, with a variety of possible reasons or causes of this gap, and a variety of ideas on how to tackle this situation!</description></item><item><title>How Often Should You Be Having Sex?</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/how-often-should-you-be-having-sex/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/how-often-should-you-be-having-sex/</guid><description>*This post contains affiliate links. I think two big questions that married couples, especially newlyweds, have on their minds when it comes to sex are:
How often or frequent should we be having sex? Does more sex make for a happier marriage? I’m going to give some insight that can help answer these two questions if you have been asking them yourself!
THE FACTS + FINDINGS There are several studies that have been done out there to determine what the &amp;ldquo;magic number&amp;rdquo; is for answering this question.</description></item><item><title>Video: Books I Recommend For Sexual Intimacy Help</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/video-books-i-recommend-for-sexual-intimacy-help/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/video-books-i-recommend-for-sexual-intimacy-help/</guid><description>*This post contains affiliate links.
In March I did a live video on Facebook talking about different books on sexual intimacy that I would recommend to couples. There was great feedback on that video, and it sounded like several people appreciated it! So I wanted to make sure it was published on my website for others to access as well.
I only share three books in this video, but I think they are so great for helping couples enrich their sexual intimacy, whether this part of their marriage is heavily struggling, or they could just use some more insight.</description></item><item><title>Taking Responsibility For Your Sexuality</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/taking-responsibility-for-your-sexuality/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/taking-responsibility-for-your-sexuality/</guid><description>*This post contains affiliate links.
I think one of the biggest hangups a couple can have when it comes to their sex life is not understanding their own sexuality first. It makes me sad that so many married people don’t even understand this huge part of their life and who they are. Which is like, the basis of a satisfying sex life for both husband and wife!
Why it&amp;rsquo;s important SOOOO I want to talk just a little bit about this.</description></item><item><title>Selflessness: The Key to Great Emotional &amp; Physical Intimacy</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/selflessness-the-key-to-great-emotional-physical-intimacy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/selflessness-the-key-to-great-emotional-physical-intimacy/</guid><description>*This post contains affiliate links.
I truly believe in selflessness. I’ve spoken about this before on different videos and blog post topics because pride or selflessness influences every single aspect of marriage!
I believe that when both spouses are being selfless, it can begin this beautiful cycle of deeper connection and more physical satisfaction. What was that last feeling? Physical satisfaction? YEP. Let’s talk about it!
To apply this “cycle” to sexual intimacy, if you are putting your spouse first, wanting them to have a satisfying experience, they will want to give you a satisfying experience right back.</description></item><item><title>The Sexy Dice Game</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/the-sexy-dice-game/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/the-sexy-dice-game/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share this idea with you guys because I think it&amp;rsquo;s a fun, EASY way to switch things up when it comes to your sex life!
For whatever reason, we all experience a hiatus of sexual intimacy at times. Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s because there are natural life transitions happening like having a baby, and other times you&amp;rsquo;re just needing a nudge to get back there. This game can be that nudge for your marriage!</description></item><item><title>An Affair is an Extremely Stupid Idea</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/an-affair-is-an-extremely-stupid-idea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/an-affair-is-an-extremely-stupid-idea/</guid><description>You may not have needed me to tell you that but there are 39 million people in the world and I&amp;rsquo;m sure millions more, who needed to be told that this week.
I&amp;rsquo;m always thinking about how current events are affecting marriages, so of course I have been thinking about this whole Ashley Madison hack recently. Call me naive but I didn&amp;rsquo;t really know there were website services for cheating until a few years ago, when I saw a billboard advertisement for one.</description></item><item><title>Save it For Your Husband - Part Two</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/save-it-for-your-husband-part-two/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/save-it-for-your-husband-part-two/</guid><description>Feel free to LISTEN to this blog post below!
[sc name=&amp;ldquo;soundcloud&amp;rdquo; id=&amp;ldquo;273882598&amp;rdquo; ]
There have been some interesting findings that have come from a blog post I wrote a few months ago, and I would like to share those with you.
A few months back, I wrote my long-held opinion on bikinis, in the post: &amp;ldquo;Save it For Your Husband.&amp;rdquo; I suggest reading it if you haven&amp;rsquo;t yet, as it can shed some more light on this current post.</description></item><item><title>Save It For Your Husband</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/save-it-for-your-husband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/save-it-for-your-husband/</guid><description>Feel free to LISTEN to this blog post below!
[sc name=&amp;ldquo;soundcloud&amp;rdquo; id=&amp;ldquo;273881414&amp;rdquo; ]
I don&amp;rsquo;t like bikinis, I don&amp;rsquo;t wear them. I think they are immodest and inappropriate and impractical to be wearing swimming. I have read a few articles the past month, that have lead me to feel strongly about sharing why I feel this way about bikinis. One of those articles was, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not celebrating bikini season this year&amp;rdquo; by Kit Steinkellner.</description></item><item><title>Pornography: A Huge Threat To Marriage</title><link>https://freshlymarried.com/pornography-a-huge-threat-to-marriage/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://freshlymarried.com/pornography-a-huge-threat-to-marriage/</guid><description>Pornography is one of the biggest threats to marriages and families. Sex is the number 1 topic searched on the Internet (NCPCE Online, &amp;ldquo;Current Statistics,&amp;rdquo; Internet, http://www.nationalcoalition.org/stat.html). The American Academy of Matrimonial Lawyers reported the biggest factors in divorce cases:
 68% of the divorces involved one party meeting a new lover over the Internet.  56% involved one party having &amp;ldquo;an obsessive interest in pornographic websites.&amp;rdquo; These statistics are disgusting and sad.</description></item></channel></rss>